{"filename": "compiled_rocks.xls_Rock Database.csv", "header": ["Rock Category", "Rock Type", "Graphic", "Texture", "Minerals\nPresent", "Chemical Composition", "Color", "Structure", "Notes", "Researcher"], "content": [["igneous", "granite", "", "fine-medium", "quartz\nfeldspar mica", "70-77% silica, 11-13% alumina, 3-5% potassium oxide, 3-5% soda, 1% lime, 2-3% total iron, and less than 1% magnesia and titania", "white\nlight gray\npink\nyellow", "non-foliated", "sometimes has large feldspar crystals", "B. Folmer"], ["sedimentary", "limestone", "", "fine", "Calcite", "CaCO3 (calcium carbonate) made up of 56.0 per cent CaO (lime) and 44 per cent CO2 (carbon dioxide).", "white\nlight gray to\nblack", "thin layers", "soft fizzes in acid\nsometimes has fossils", "B. Folmer"], ["metamorphic", "gneiss", "", "coarse", "white feldspar\nblack mica\nsilvery mica", "70-77% silica, 11-13% alumina, 3-5% potassium oxide, 3-5% soda, 1% lime, 2-3% total iron, and less than 1% magnesia and titania", "gray", "well foliated", "parallel bands of white and dark minerals, very hard", "B. Folmer"], ["Igneous", "Obsidian", "", "glassy", "quartz, biotite, oligoclase", "chemical", "Black", "non-foliated", "", "Donna Pirog"], ["sedimentary", "shale", "", "fine", "clay particles hydrated aluminium and iron oxides", "biologic", "brown          tan             rusty", "foliated", "consolidated mud, rich in organic matter", "D. Pirog"], ["metamorphic", "slate", "", "fine", "clay particles hydrated aluminium and iron oxides", "clastic", "brown           tan                rusty", "foliated", "A product of low-grade metamorphism of shale or mudstone.", "D. Pirog"], ["sedimentary", "sandstone", "", "medium", "Quartz", "clastic", "tan               brownish", "non-foliated", "consolidated sand", "D. Pirog"], ["Igneous", "granite", "", "porphyritic", "Quartz        mica                    feldspar", "chemical", "pink              green            black             tan               brown", "non-foliated", "magmatic extrusive", "D. Pirog"], ["sedimentary", "sandstone", "", "coarse", "quartz\nsilica\ncalcium carbonate\niron oxide", "", "red\ngray\nwhite\nyellow", "foliated", "Encarta 2001", "D. Tarwater"], ["sedimentary", "shale", "", "fine", "mica\nclay", "", "gray\nred\npink\nbrown\nblack", "foliated", "Encarta 2001", "D. Tarwater"], ["igneous", "granite", "", "porphyritic", "feldspar\nquartz\nmica", "", "white\ngray", "non-foliated", "Encarta 2001", "D. Tarwater"], ["Igneous", "Obsidian", "", "glassy", "35% Quartz 63% feldspar", "", "black, gray, reddish brown", "Prominent conchoidal fractures", "Occurs as volcanic lava flows", "J. Wolner"], ["Fossil", "Petrified Wood", "", "smooth", "", "", "reddish brown", "", "found in Elizabeth, CO", "J. Wolner"], ["Sedimentary", "Sandstone", "", "medium", "quartz", "", "Varies", "", "Used principaly in construction", "J. Wolner"], ["igenous", "gabbro", "", "fine-coarse", "plagioclase, pyroxene, olivine, biotite", "48% silicon dioxide\n17% aluminum oxide\n13% iron oxides\n11% calcium oxide\n8% magnesium oxide\n3% sodium oxide", "gray-black\nwhite-gray\nbrownish\ngreenish", "no layering", "magmatic intrusive, basic", "R. Hawke"], ["igenous", "basalt", "", "fine", "plagioclase, amphibole, olivine, augite", "48% silicon dioxide\n17% aluminum oxide\n13% iron oxides\n11% calcium oxide\n8% magnesium oxide\n3% sodium oxide", "black\ngreenish,\ndark green,\ndark gray", "no layering", "magmatic extrusive, basic", "R. Hawke"], ["igenous", "obsidian", "", "glassy", "quartz, biotite, oligoclase", "76% silicas\n13% iron oxides\n11% calcium oxide", "black\ndark gray\nbrown", "cracks present", "magmatic extrusive, basic", "R. Hawke"]], "target": "deex", "label": "8", "table_NE": [[], [], [], [], ["PERCENT", "PERCENT"], ["PERCENT", "PERCENT", "PERCENT", "PERCENT", "PERCENT", "PERCENT", "PERCENT", "PERCENT", "PERCENT", "PERCENT", "PERCENT", "PERCENT", "PERCENT", "PERCENT", "PERCENT", "PERCENT", "PERCENT", "PERCENT", "PERCENT", "PERCENT", "PERCENT", "PERCENT", "PERCENT", "PERCENT", "PERCENT", "PERCENT", "PERCENT", "PERCENT", "PERCENT", "PERCENT", "PERCENT"], [], [], ["DATE", "PRODUCT", "DATE", "EVENT", "DATE", "GPE", "GPE"], ["PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON"]], "most_common": ["EMPTY", "EMPTY", "EMPTY", "EMPTY", "PERCENT", "PERCENT", "EMPTY", "EMPTY", "WORK_OF_ART", "PERSON1"], "related_table": ["compiled_rocks.xls_Rock Database.csv"]}