{"filename": "00fbadb4-45a0-4853-89ea-362eab8bb900.xlsx_Sheet1.csv", "header": ["", "TOPIC", "SPEAKER", "CE HOURS APPROVED", "HOURS ATTENDED"], "content": [["", "How will the future be measured?", "Armin Weinberg, PhD", "", ""], ["", "Accelerating Oncology Research: How Baylor Health Care System is Using Registries to Improve Cancer Research Analytics", "John Preskitt, MD", "", ""], ["", "The ONC Vision for Health Information Technology & Public Health", "James Daniel, MPH", "", ""], ["", "IBM Watson: Transforming Cancer Data & Healthcare", "Rob High Jr., IBM Fellow", "", ""], ["08:00:00", "NAACCR Now", "Maureen MacIntyre", "1", ""], ["", "A Vision for Using Health IT To Meet Cancer Survivors' Needs", "Naveen Rao", "", ""], ["", "Survivorship & Passport to Care", "Marc Horowitz", "", ""], ["08:00:00", "Birds of a Feather: The Future of Cancer Surveillance….or Not?", "Susan Gershman; Rich Pinder", "1", ""], ["", "Comparative Effectiveness Research & Cancer Screening", "James Goodwin, MD", "", ""], ["", "Comparative Effectiveness of Granulocyte Growth Factors Among elderly Patients with Non-Hodgkin's Lymphoma", "Linda Elting, DrPH", "", ""], ["13:00:00", "Plenary Session 5: NAACCR Update on Steering Committees", "Antoinette Stroup, BS, MS, PhD; Maureen MacIntyre MHSA", "0.75", ""], ["15:30:00", "NAACCR Showcase", "", "1", ""], ["", "Virtual Pooled Data Project", "Dennis Deapen, DrPH", "", ""], ["", "Development & Demonstration of CI* Rank", "E. Feuer, PhD", "", ""]], "target": "deex", "label": "1", "table_NE": [["TIME", "TIME", "TIME", "TIME"], ["ORG", "WORK_OF_ART", "ORG", "WORK_OF_ART", "CARDINAL"], ["PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "ORG", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON"], [], []], "most_common": ["TIME", "ORG", "PERSON2", "EMPTY", "EMPTY"], "related_table": ["00fbadb4-45a0-4853-89ea-362eab8bb900.xlsx_Sheet1.csv"]}