{"filename": "board-smt-business-expenses-15-16.xlsx_M Helliwell.csv", "header": ["National Institute for Health and Care Excellence", "", "", "", "", "", ""], "content": [["Board and Senior Management Team Business Expenses for the Financial Year 2015-16", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Margaret Helliwell - Clinical Practice Centre Director", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["This report shows business expenses incurred by the incumbent in delivery of their duties. NICE holds Board meetings around the country closer to the organisations and people we support. All staff including Directors are required to travel standard class when travelling by rail. Air travel within the UK or Europe, and flights of less than 8 hours in duration will always be in economy class. Long haul (outside Europe or flights of over 8 hours duration) can be booked in business class. Hotel costs are for 1 night unless otherwise stated.", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Source", "Date of Expense", "Location", "Purpose", "Funded", "Type of Expenditure", "Value"], ["Redfern Travel", "4/2/15", "Keighley to Zone U1* London", "Meetings in London", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£31.02"], ["Redfern Travel", "4/2/15", "Zone U1* London to Skipton", "Meetings in London", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£50.52"], ["Redfern Travel", "4/2/15", "Zone U1* London to Grange-over-Sands", "London meetings", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£67.25"], ["Redfern Travel", "4/15/15", "Keighley to Manchester Piccadilly", "Meetings in Manchester", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£18.35"], ["Redfern Travel", "4/28/15", "Keighley to Zone U1* Londn", "Meetings in London", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "-£66.39"], ["Redfern Travel", "4/28/15", "Grange Portland", "Meetings in London", "NICE", "Hotels", "£126.39"], ["Redfern Travel", "4/28/15", "Keighley to Zone U1* London", "Meetings in London", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£74.23"], ["Redfern Travel", "5/19/15", "Keighley to Zone U1* Londn", "Meetings in London", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£50.99"], ["Redfern Travel", "5/19/15", "Zone U1* Londn to Bristol", "May Board Meeting", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£66.70"], ["Redfern Travel", "5/20/15", "Bristol Temple Meads to Keighley", "May Board Meeting", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£73.73"], ["Interface event Management", "5/20/15", "Bristol", "May Board Meeting - Dinner", "NICE", "Subsistence", "£30.00"], ["Interface event Management", "5/20/15", "Bristol", "May Board Meeting - Bed and Breakfast", "NICE", "Hotels", "£105.00"], ["Redfern Travel", "6/17/15", "Zone U1* Londn to Keighley", "Meetings in London", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£50.99"], ["Redfern Travel", "6/25/15", "Keighley to ZONE U1*LONDN", "Meetings in London", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£20.45"], ["Redfern Travel", "6/25/15", "Travelodge London Covent Garden", "London Heathrow", "NICE", "Hotels", "£103.05"], ["Redfern Travel", "6/26/15", "Zone U1* London to Grange-over-Sands", "London meetings", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£67.25"], ["Redfern Travel", "7/1/15", "Keighley to Zone U1* Londn", "Meetings in London", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£107.21"], ["Redfern Travel", "7/13/15", "Keighley to Haymarket", "July Board Meeting", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£63.79"], ["Redfern Travel", "7/15/15", "Haymarket to Keighley", "July Board Meeting", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£32.46"], ["Interface event Management", "7/15/15", "Edinburgh", "July Board Meeting - Dinner", "NICE", "Subsistence", "£25.00"], ["Interface event Management", "7/15/15", "Edinburgh", "July Board Meeting - Bed and Breakfast", "NICE", "Hotels", "£105.00"], ["Redfern Travel", "8/11/15", "Travelodge London Covent Garden", "London Heathrow", "NICE", "Hotels", "-£101.65"], ["Redfern Travel", "8/11/15", "Travelodge London Covent Garden", "London Heathrow", "NICE", "Hotels", "£103.05"], ["Redfern Travel", "8/11/15", "Keighley to Zone U1* Londn", "Meetings in London", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£117.25"], ["Redfern Travel", "8/19/15", "Shipley (yorks) to ZONE U1*LONDN", "Meetings in London", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "-£58.19"], ["Redfern Travel", "8/19/15", "Shipley (yorks) to ZONE U1*LONDN", "Meetings in London", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "-£32.24"], ["Redfern Travel", "8/19/15", "Shipley to Zone U1* Londn", "Meetings in London", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£112.14"], ["Redfern Travel", "8/19/15", "Shipley to Zone U1* Londn", "Meetings in London", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£145.46"], ["Redfern Travel", "9/1/15", "Shipley to Zone U1* Londn", "Meetings in London", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£152.84"], ["Redfern Travel", "9/4/15", "Shipley to Zone U1* Londn", "Meetings in London", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£153.92"], ["Redfern Travel", "9/15/15", "Keighley to Lincoln Central", "September Board Meeting", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£15.87"], ["Redfern Travel", "9/15/15", "Zone U1*   Londn to Lincoln Central", "September Board Meeting", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£46.04"], ["Redfern Travel", "9/15/15", "Keighley to Zone U1* Londn", "Meetings in London", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£77.90"], ["Interface event Management", "9/16/15", "Lincoln", "September Board Meeting - Dinner", "NICE", "Subsistence", "£30.00"], ["Interface event Management", "9/16/15", "Lincoln", "September Board Meeeting - Bed and Breakfast", "NICE", "Hotels", "£95.00"], ["Redfern Travel", "10/12/15", "Keighley to Liverpool Lime Street", "Meetings in London", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£29.18"], ["Redfern Travel", "10/21/15", "Keighley to ZONE U1*LONDN", "Meetings in London", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£80.47"], ["Redfern Travel", "10/28/15", "Keighley to ZONE U1*LONDN", "Meetings in London", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£117.25"], ["Redfern Travel", "11/17/15", "London Victoria to Clapham Junction", "November 2015 Public Board Meeting", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£3.75"], ["Redfern Travel", "11/17/15", "Keighley to ZONE U1*LONDN", "Meetings in London", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£19.32"], ["Interface event Management", "11/18/15", "London ", "November Board Meeting - Dinner", "NICE", "Subsistence", "£25.00"], ["Redfern Travel", "11/18/15", "Zone U123* Londn to Keighley", "Meetings in London", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£78.10"], ["Redfern Travel", "12/16/15", "Shipley (yorks) to ZONE U1*LONDN", "Meetings in London", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£152.79"], ["Uniglobe", "3/16/16", "Nha-Trang", "Meetings with Vietnamese government", "NICE International", "Flight", "£88.94"]], "target": "0", "label": "Source", "table_NE": [["DATE", "PERSON", "ORG", "GPE", "LOC", "TIME", "LOC", "TIME", "TIME", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "QUANTITY", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "ORG", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "ORG", "GPE", "GPE", "ORG", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "FAC", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "FAC", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "FAC"], ["GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "DATE", "EVENT", "DATE", "DATE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "FAC", "GPE", "GPE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "GPE", "FAC", "GPE", "FAC", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "DATE", "DATE", "GPE", "DATE", "DATE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "DATE", "GPE", "DATE", "GPE", "GPE", "NORP"], [], [], ["MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY"]], "most_common": ["ORG", "CARDINAL", "GPE", "GPE", "EMPTY", "EMPTY", "MONEY"]}