{"filename": "hosb1112-tabs.xls_Table 2.01.csv", "header": ["Table 2.01 ", "Stops and searches made under s44(1) and (2) of the Terrorism Act 2000 by police force area1,2", "", "", ""], "content": [["Number", "", "", "", "Great Britain"], ["", "", "Year of search", "", ""], ["Police force area2", "", "2009/10", "2010/11", "2011/12"], ["Cheshire", "", "20", "-", "-"], ["Cumbria", "", "65", "-", "-"], ["Essex", "", "389", "29", "-"], ["Greater Manchester", "", "151", "26", "-"], ["Hampshire", "", "53", "-", "-"], ["London, City Of", "", "1,386", "651", "-"], ["Merseyside", "", "4", "-", "-"], ["Metropolitan Police", "", "81,474", "7,853", "-"], ["North Yorkshire", "", "154", "29", "-"], ["South Wales", "", "210", "90", "-"], ["Sussex3", "", "1,260", "232", "-"], ["Thames Valley", "", "144", "19", "-"], ["England and Wales", "", "85,310", "8,929", "-"], ["British Transport Police4", "", "17,135", "798", "-"], ["Scotland", "", "59", "17", "-"], ["Great Britain", "", "102,504", "9,744", "-"], ["Source: Home Office, British Transport Police and Scottish Police Forces.", "", "", "", ""], ["1.  Does not include 'vehicle only' searches.", "", "", "", ""], ["2.  Only police forces in England and Wales that conducted section 44 searches between 1 January 2010 and 31 April 2012 are separately identified in the table.", "", "", "", ""], ["3.  Sussex Police cannot separate 'vehicle only' searches from vehicle and occupant searches; as a consequence data here cover searches of pedestrians only.", "", "", "", ""]], "target": "0", "label": "Number", "table_NE": [["GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "ORG", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "ORG", "GPE", "GPE", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "CARDINAL", "GPE", "GPE", "CARDINAL", "DATE", "ORG"], [], ["DATE", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["GPE", "DATE"]], "most_common": ["GPE", "EMPTY", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "GPE"]}