{"filename": "Housing-in-London-tables-2017.xls_4.1 Finding housing and jobs.csv", "header": ["#", "4.1", ""], "content": [["Chart title", "Public opinion on ease of finding housing and jobs in major European cities, 2015", ""], ["Sources and notes", "- EU Commission, Quality of Life in European Cities 2015", ""], ["City", "Net agreement that it is easy to find good housing at a reasonable price", "Net agreement that it is easy to find a job"], ["Greater Paris", "-85", "25"], ["Berlin", "-74", "5"], ["London", "-72", "19"], ["Istanbul", "-61", "15"], ["Rome", "-53", "-31"], ["Madrid", "-4", "-49"], ["Lisbon", "-24", "-17"], ["Amsterdam", "-48", "3"]], "target": "0", "label": "City", "table_NE": [["GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE"], ["NORP", "DATE", "ORG", "DATE"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"]], "most_common": ["GPE", "DATE", "CARDINAL"]}