{"filename": "1fc6cae1-cd39-43df-a066-d4c624819061.xls_pnamesstra-sull.csv", "header": ["STRAFFORD COUNTY/NAMES ON CHECKLIST", "", "", "", "", "", ""], "content": [["", "Democratic", "Republican", "Undeclared", "Total", "", "#1"], ["Barrington", "1888.0", "1846.0", "2623.0", "6357.0", "", "518.0"], ["Dover Ward 1", "1510.0", "623.0", "1457.0", "3590.0", "", "697.0"], ["Dover Ward 2", "1372.0", "712.0", "1301.0", "3385.0", "", "561.0"], ["Dover Ward 3", "1337.0", "1082.0", "1455.0", "3874.0", "", "314.0"], ["Dover Ward 4", "1461.0", "978.0", "1266.0", "3705.0", "", "400.0"], ["Dover Ward 5", "1147.0", "741.0", "1312.0", "3200.0", "", "413.0"], ["Dover Ward 6", "1144.0", "861.0", "1295.0", "3300.0", "", "312.0"], ["Durham", "4033.0", "1674.0", "4665.0", "10372.0", "", "1829.0"], ["Farmington", "1387.0", "1263.0", "1901.0", "4551.0", "", "403.0"], ["Lee", "1248.0", "785.0", "1246.0", "3279.0", "", "226.0"], ["Madbury", "448.0", "314.0", "635.0", "1397.0", "", "125.0"], ["Middleton", "284.0", "311.0", "494.0", "1089.0", "", "119.0"], ["Milton", "864.0", "936.0", "1409.0", "3209.0", "", "323.0"], ["New Durham", "486.0", "685.0", "873.0", "2044.0", "", "128.0"], ["Rochester Ward 1", "1233.0", "1081.0", "1602.0", "3916.0", "", "433.0"], ["Rochester Ward 2", "1014.0", "954.0", "1302.0", "3270.0", "", "330.0"], ["Rochester Ward 3", "1203.0", "1178.0", "1280.0", "3661.0", "", "425.0"], ["Rochester Ward 4", "1143.0", "838.0", "1251.0", "3232.0", "", "349.0"], ["Rochester Ward 5", "1054.0", "1016.0", "1389.0", "3459.0", "", "345.0"], ["Rochester Ward 6", "1083.0", "758.0", "1182.0", "3023.0", "", "389.0"], ["Rollinsford", "681.0", "481.0", "938.0", "2100.0", "", "128.0"], ["Somersworth Ward 1", "688.0", "425.0", "738.0", "1851.0", "", "192.0"], ["Somersworth Ward 2*", "556.0", "279.0", "760.0", "1595.0", "", "182.0"], ["Somersworth Ward 3", "514.0", "304.0", "661.0", "1479.0", "", "162.0"], ["Somersworth Ward 4", "709.0", "413.0", "791.0", "1913.0", "", "164.0"], ["Somersworth Ward 5", "462.0", "208.0", "603.0", "1273.0", "", "147.0"], ["Strafford", "786.0", "987.0", "1471.0", "3244.0", "", "175.0"], ["Totals", "29735.0", "21733.0", "35900.0", "87368.0", "", "9789.0"], ["", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["*corrected numbers rec'd from city clerk 12/9/8", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["SULLIVAN COUNTY/NAMES ON CHECKLIST", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "Democratic", "Republican", "Undeclared", "Total", "", "#1"], ["Acworth", "167.0", "145.0", "442.0", "754.0", "", "39.0"], ["Charlestown", "1075.0", "752.0", "1598.0", "3425.0", "", "247.0"], ["Claremont Ward 1*", "1001.0", "623.0", "938.0", "2562.0", "", "249.0"], ["Claremont Ward 2*", "1198.0", "933.0", "926.0", "3057.0", "", "275.0"], ["Claremont Ward 3*", "964.0", "656.0", "1182.0", "2802.0", "", "259.0"], ["Cornish", "503.0", "298.0", "435.0", "1236.0", "", "86.0"], ["Croydon", "99.0", "177.0", "218.0", "494.0", "", "40.0"], ["Goshen", "163.0", "177.0", "253.0", "593.0", "", "49.0"], ["Grantham", "666.0", "678.0", "987.0", "2331.0", "", "109.0"], ["Langdon", "116.0", "225.0", "144.0", "485.0", "", "31.0"], ["Lempster", "161.0", "186.0", "429.0", "776.0", "", "64.0"], ["Newport", "1162.0", "1338.0", "1673.0", "4173.0", "", "341.0"], ["Plainfield", "586.0", "349.0", "786.0", "1721.0", "", "125.0"], ["Springfield", "193.0", "301.0", "437.0", "931.0", "", "58.0"], ["Sunapee", "499.0", "785.0", "1420.0", "2704.0", "", "137.0"], ["Unity", "285.0", "235.0", "527.0", "1047.0", "", "77.0"], ["Washington", "128.0", "260.0", "395.0", "783.0", "", "45.0"], ["Totals", "8966.0", "8118.0", "12790.0", "29874.0", "", "2231.0"], ["*corrections rec'd from clerks - corrections made 1/15/9", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["1. Number of persons who registered to vote at the polling place", "", "", "", "", "", ""]], "target": "4", "label": "Total", "table_NE": [["GPE", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "GPE", "GPE", "ORG", "GPE", "ORG", "CARDINAL", "GPE", "CARDINAL", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "CARDINAL", "GPE", "CARDINAL", "GPE", "CARDINAL", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "CARDINAL"], ["NORP", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "NORP", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["NORP", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "NORP", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], [], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"]], "most_common": ["GPE", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "EMPTY", "CARDINAL"]}