{"filename": "errol_mclaughlin_jr__10001__DKR_400bp_11-19-01.xlsx_GasDailyVal.csv", "header": ["Deal Date", "Deal #", "Code", "", "Term Start", "Term End", "Volume", "Price", "Nov 1-9 Price", "MTM", "", "DATE", "GDP-KERN/RIVER", "", "DATE", "GDP-HEHUB"], "content": [["2001-10-23 00:00:00", "YD6643", "Kern", "DKR Sells", "2001-11-01 00:00:00", "2001-11-30 00:00:00", "-10000", "2.37", "2.246", "-11160.00000000001", "", "2001-11-01 00:00:00", "2.725", "", "2001-11-01 00:00:00", "3.07"], ["2001-10-24 00:00:00", "YD7298", "Kern", "DKR Sells", "2001-11-01 00:00:00", "2001-11-30 00:00:00", "-10000", "2.39", "2.246", "-12960.000000000011", "", "2001-11-02 00:00:00", "2.45", "", "2001-11-02 00:00:00", "3.005"], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "-20000", "2.38", "", "", "", "2001-11-03 00:00:00", "2.115", "", "2001-11-03 00:00:00", "2.96"], ["2001-10-30 00:00:00", "YF6408", "Kern", "DKR Buys", "2001-11-01 00:00:00", "2001-11-30 00:00:00", "10000", "2.605", "2.246", "32310", "", "2001-11-04 00:00:00", "2.115", "", "2001-11-04 00:00:00", "2.96"], ["2001-11-08 00:00:00", "YI5216", "Kern", "DKR Buys", "2001-11-10 00:00:00", "2001-11-30 00:00:00", "10000", "2.08", "", "", "", "2001-11-05 00:00:00", "2.115", "", "2001-11-05 00:00:00", "2.96"], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "20000", "2.3425000000000002", "", "", "", "2001-11-06 00:00:00", "2.22", "", "2001-11-06 00:00:00", "2.885"], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "2001-11-07 00:00:00", "2.22", "", "2001-11-07 00:00:00", "2.75"], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "2001-11-08 00:00:00", "2.255", "", "2001-11-08 00:00:00", "2.735"], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "2001-11-09 00:00:00", "2", "", "2001-11-09 00:00:00", "2.725"], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "2.2461111111111114", "", "", "2.894444444444445"], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "Nov 1-9 Price", "MTM", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["2001-10-23 00:00:00", "YD6643", "HH", "DKR Buys", "2001-11-01 00:00:00", "2001-11-30 00:00:00", "10000", "2.66", "2.894", "-21060", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["2001-10-24 00:00:00", "YD7298", "HH", "DKR Buys", "2001-11-01 00:00:00", "2001-11-30 00:00:00", "10000", "2.67", "2.894", "-20160.00000000002", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "20000", "2.665", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["2001-10-30 00:00:00", "YF6408", "HH", "DKR Sells", "2001-11-01 00:00:00", "2001-11-30 00:00:00", "-10000", "3.08", "2.894", "-16739.999999999996", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["2001-11-08 00:00:00", "YI5216", "HH", "DKR Sells", "2001-11-10 00:00:00", "2001-11-30 00:00:00", "-10000", "2.78", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "-20000", "2.9299999999999997", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Kern MTM, 10-30 Nov", "-15749.99999999985", "DKR Sells 20,000 per day for 20 days at avg. Price of 2.38 and buys same vol. Back at avg. Price of 2.343", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["HH MTM, 10-30 Nov", "-111299.99999999987", "DKR Buys 20,000 per day for 20 days at avg. Price of 2.665 and sells same vol. Back at avg. Price of 2.93", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Kern MTM 1-9", "8189.999999999978", "DKR Sells 20,000 per day for 9 days at average price of 2.665 which settles against 2.246;buys 10,000 per day for 9 days at 2.605 which settles agains 2.246", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["HH MTM 1-9", "-57960.000000000015", "DKR Buys 20,000 per day for 9 days at average price of 2.665 which settles against 2.894;sells 10,000 per day for 9 days at 3.08 which settles against 2.894", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Total", "-176819.99999999977", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Libor +400 bp total", "-495001.39443410473", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""]], "target": "2", "label": "Code", "table_NE": [["DATE", "TIME", "DATE", "TIME", "DATE", "TIME", "DATE", "TIME", "DATE", "TIME", "DATE", "TIME", "DATE", "TIME", "DATE", "TIME", "ORG", "DATE", "ORG", "DATE", "ORG", "CARDINAL", "PRODUCT", "CARDINAL", "ORG", "CARDINAL", "PRODUCT"], [], ["PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "ORG", "CARDINAL", "DATE", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "ORG", "MONEY", "DATE", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "ORG", "MONEY", "DATE", "CARDINAL", "MONEY", "DATE", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "ORG", "MONEY", "DATE", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "DATE", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG"], ["DATE", "TIME", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "TIME", "DATE", "TIME", "DATE", "TIME", "DATE", "TIME", "DATE", "TIME", "DATE", "TIME", "DATE", "DATE", "TIME"], ["DATE", "TIME", "DATE", "DATE", "TIME", "TIME", "DATE", "TIME", "DATE", "DATE", "TIME", "TIME", "DATE", "TIME", "TIME", "DATE", "DATE", "TIME", "DATE", "DATE", "TIME", "TIME", "DATE", "DATE", "TIME", "TIME"], [], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "DATE", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], [], [], ["DATE", "TIME", "DATE", "TIME", "DATE", "TIME", "DATE", "TIME", "DATE", "TIME", "DATE", "TIME", "DATE", "TIME", "DATE", "TIME", "DATE"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], [], ["DATE", "TIME", "DATE", "TIME", "DATE", "TIME", "DATE", "TIME", "DATE", "TIME", "DATE", "TIME", "DATE", "TIME", "DATE", "TIME", "DATE"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"]], "most_common": ["DATE", "EMPTY", "CARDINAL", "ORG", "DATE", "DATE", "EMPTY", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "EMPTY", "EMPTY", "DATE", "CARDINAL", "EMPTY", "DATE", "CARDINAL"]}