{"filename": "0c1b1da4-791b-4cd1-9bc2-0da6e98d4cbe.xls_West Oahu Peer.csv", "header": ["UNIVERSITY OF HAWAI‘I - WEST O‘AHU", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], "content": [["PEER GROUP  1/", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "Institution", "", "", "City", "", "State", "", "", "1994 Carnegie Classification", "", "", "2000 Carnegie Classification", "", "", "Unit ID", "", "", "FICE", "", "", "URL"], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "1.0", "California State University - Monterey Bay  2/", "", "", "Seaside", "", "CA", "", "", "", "", "", "Baccalaureate Colleges - Liberal Arts", "", "", "409698.0", "", "", "32603.0", "", "", "www.csumb.edu"], ["", "2.0", "Eastern Oregon University", "", "", "La Grande", "", "OR", "", "", "Baccalaureate Colleges II", "", "", "Master's Colleges & Universities II", "", "", "208646.0", "", "", "3193.0", "", "", "www.eou.edu"], ["", "3.0", "Evergreen State College", "", "", "Olympia", "", "WA", "", "", "Baccalaureate Colleges II", "", "", "Baccalaureate Colleges - Liberal Arts", "", "", "235167.0", "", "", "8155.0", "", "", "www.evergreen.edu"], ["", "4.0", "Great Basin College", "", "", "Elko", "", "NV", "", "", "Associate of Arts Colleges", "", "", "Associate's Colleges", "", "", "182306.0", "", "", "6977.0", "", "", "www.gbcnv.edu"], ["", "5.0", "Texas A&M University - Texarkana", "", "", "Texarkana", "", "TX", "", "", "Master's (Comprehensive) Colleges & Universities I", "", "", "Master's Colleges & Universities I", "", "", "224545.0", "", "", "31703.0", "", "", "www.tamut.edu"], ["", "6.0", "University of Hawai‘i at Hilo", "", "", "Hilo", "", "HI", "", "", "Baccalaureate Colleges II", "", "", "Baccalaureate Colleges - Liberal Arts", "", "", "141565.0", "", "", "1611.0", "", "", "www.uhh.hawaii.edu"], ["", "7.0", "University of Washington - Bothell Campus  3/", "", "", "Bothell", "", "WA", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "377555.0", "", "", "", "", "", "www.washington.edu"], ["", "8.0", "University of Washington - Tacoma Campus  3/", "", "", "Tacoma", "", "WA", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "377564.0", "", "", "", "", "", "www.washington.edu"], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "University of Hawai‘i - West O‘ahu", "", "", "Pearl City", "", "HI", "", "", "Baccalaureate Colleges II", "", "", "Baccalaureate Colleges - Liberal Arts", "", "", "141981.0", "", "", "21078.0", "", "", "www.uhwo.hawaii.edu"], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "Note:  University of Hawai‘i - West O‘ahu peer group listing was developed by the University of Hawai‘i Office of Planning & Policy, University of Hawai‘i Institutional Research Office, and University of Hawai‘i - West O‘ahu officials.", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "1/  Benchmark comparison group for University of Hawai‘i - West O‘ahu is not available.", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "2/  California State University - Monterey Bay was established in 1994; 1994 Carnegie Classification not available.", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "3/  FICE and Carnegie classification not available; campus is not listed in the Higher Education Directory or the Carnegie Foundation electronic data file.", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "Sources:", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "Peer Group Listing:  University of Hawai‘i Office of Planning & Policy, University of Hawai‘i Institutional Research Office, University of Hawai‘i - West O‘ahu, January 2002", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "Institution Names, Campus Locations, Unit ID, and FICE:  Higher Education Directory, 2004", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "Carnegie Classifications:  Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching, \"The Carnegie Classification of Institutions of Higher Education, 2000 Edition,\" Electronic Data File, 2000", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "Peer Group Listing last updated:  January 2002", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "Peer Institution Information last updated:  October 2004", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""]], "target": "2", "label": "Institution", "table_NE": [[], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "DATE", "DATE", "ORG", "ORG", "WORK_OF_ART", "ORG", "DATE", "DATE"], ["ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "DATE", "DATE", "WORK_OF_ART", "DATE"], [], [], ["GPE", "FAC", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE"], [], ["NORP", "GPE", "NORP", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "NORP"], [], [], ["DATE", "ORG", "WORK_OF_ART"], [], [], ["DATE", "WORK_OF_ART", "WORK_OF_ART"], [], [], [], [], [], [], [], [], []], "most_common": ["EMPTY", "ORG", "ORG", "EMPTY", "EMPTY", "GPE", "EMPTY", "GPE", "EMPTY", "EMPTY", "DATE", "EMPTY", "EMPTY", "WORK_OF_ART", "EMPTY", "EMPTY", "EMPTY", "EMPTY", "EMPTY", "EMPTY", "EMPTY", "EMPTY", "EMPTY"]}