{"filename": "board-smt-business-expenses-16-17.xlsx_S Asthana.csv", "header": ["Source", "Date of Expense", "Location", "Purpose", "Funded", "Type of Expenditure", "Value"], "content": [["Expenses", "11/16/16", "Manchester airport", "Airport parking (Exeter Airport)", "NICE", "Parking/Road Tolls", "£31.00"], ["Redfern Travel", "11/16/16", "Exeter to Manchester", "Meetings in Manchester", "NICE", "Flight", "£269.67"], ["Interface event Management", "11/29/16", "Manchester ", "November Board Meeting - Dinner, Bed and Breakfast", "NICE", "Hotels", "£99.17"], ["Expenses", "12/13/16", "NICE (LONDON)", "Car parking at Exeter train station", "NICE", "Parking/Road Tolls", "£12.00"], ["Expenses", "12/13/16", "NICE (LONDON)", "Car parking at Exeter train station ", "NICE", "Parking/Road Tolls", "£12.00"], ["Redfern Travel", "12/15/16", "Ladywell to Exeter St Davids", "December Public Board meeting", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£88.40"], ["Redfern Travel", "12/15/16", "Exeter St Davids to Lewisham", "December Public Board meeting", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£44.00"], ["Expenses", "1/5/17", "Manchester airport", "Airport parking (Exeter Airport)", "NICE", "Parking/Road Tolls", "£31.00"], ["Expenses", "1/5/17", "NICE (LONDON)", "Car parking at Exeter train station (I have a text message but no receipt)", "NICE", "Parking/Road Tolls", "£12.00"], ["Redfern Travel", "1/16/17", "Exeter St Davids to London Paddington", "Meetings in London", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£262.30"], ["Expenses", "1/17/17", "London Borough of Lewisham", "Amendment to travel to NICE Question Time & Public Board Meeting May", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£48.40"], ["Expenses", "1/18/17", "London Borough of Lewisham", "Amendment to travel from NICE Question Time & Public Board Meeting May", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£40.10"], ["Interface event Management", "1/23/17", "Lewisham ", "January Board Meeting - Bed and Breakfast", "NICE", "Hotels", "£93.33"], ["Interface event Management", "1/23/17", "Lewisham ", "January Board Meeting - Dinner", "NICE", "Subsistence", "£21.63"], ["Redfern Travel", "1/25/17", "Exeter St Davids to London Waterloo", "Meetings in London", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£157.90"], ["Expenses", "2/13/17", "London Borough of Lewisham", "I had to book an earlier train to get to London on time", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£48.40"], ["Expenses", "2/13/17", "London Borough of Lewisham", "I had to book an earlier train from London or I would have had to wait at Paddington for more than 2 hours", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£40.10"], ["Redfern Travel", "3/1/17", "Exeter St Davids to Durham", "March 2017 NICE Public Board Meeting", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£273.10"], ["Interface event Management", "3/23/17", "Durham ", "March Board Meeting - Bed and Breakfast", "NICE", "Hotels", "£82.50"], ["Interface event Management", "3/23/17", "Durham ", "March Board Meeting - Dinner", "NICE", "Subsistence", "£23.33"], ["Redfern Travel", "3/23/17", "Exeter St Davids to London Paddington", "Meetings in London", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£263.30"], ["Redfern Travel", "3/23/17", "London Charing Cross to London Paddington", "Meetings in London", "NICE", "Underground/Train/Bus", "£13.30"]], "target": "govuk", "label": "0", "table_NE": [["ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG"], ["DATE", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "DATE", "DATE"], ["GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "ORG", "GPE", "ORG", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "ORG", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE"], ["FAC", "GPE", "DATE", "GPE", "GPE", "DATE", "DATE", "FAC", "GPE", "GPE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "TIME", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "GPE", "GPE"], [], [], ["MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY"]], "most_common": ["ORG", "CARDINAL", "GPE", "GPE", "EMPTY", "EMPTY", "MONEY"], "related_table": ["board-smt-business-expenses-16-17.xlsx_S Asthana.csv", "board-smt-business-expenses-15-16.xlsx_M Helliwell.csv"]}