{"filename": "expenses-octdec2009.xls_Cleveland.csv", "header": ["DATES", "DESTINATION", "PURPOSE", "TRAVEL Air", "Rail", "Taxi/Car", "Accommodation/Meals", "OTHER (Including Hospitality Given)", "Total Cost £"], "content": [["1-2 Oct 2009", "Sunningdale", "Attendance at meeting of Top 200 civil servants at the National School of Government", "", "18.80", "", "", "", "18.80"], ["15-Oct-09", "Sunningdale", "Autumn Sunningdale", "", "9.40", "", "", "", "9.40"], ["20-Oct-09", "Margate", "Official meetings", "", "45.20", "", "", "", "45.20"], ["29-Oct-09", "Newcastle", "Civil Service in the North East Programme", "", "96.50", "", "", "", "96.50"], ["3-Dec-09", "Newcastle", "Civil Service in the North East Programme", "", "172.50", "", "", "", "172.50"], ["18-Dec-09", "Reading", "DEFRA Event", "", "35.90", "", "", "", "35.90"], ["Oct-Dec 09", "", "Home to Office travel", "242.70", "614.50", "", "", "", "857.20"]], "target": "govuk", "label": "1", "table_NE": [["DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE"], ["GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE"], ["CARDINAL", "ORG", "PERSON"], [], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], [], [], [], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"]], "most_common": ["DATE2", "GPE", "CARDINAL", "EMPTY", "CARDINAL", "EMPTY", "EMPTY", "EMPTY", "CARDINAL"], "related_table": ["expenses-octdec2009.xls_Cleveland.csv"]}