{"filename": "C10002_C10002.csv", "header": ["Regional Council by Highest Qualification(1) for the Census Usually Resident Population Count Aged 15 Years and Over", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], "content": [["2006 Census", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Regional Council", "No Qualification", "Level 1 Certificate Gained at School", "Level 2 Certificate Gained at School", "Level 3 or 4 Certificate Gained at School", "Overseas Secondary School Qualification", "Level 1, 2 or 3 Certificate Gained Post-school", "Level 4 Certificate Gained Post-school"], ["Northland Region", "31,101", "16,158", "8,694", "3,267", "3,963", "4,701", "11,625"], ["Auckland Region", "183,681", "105,348", "79,686", "60,444", "90,546", "39,534", "78,630"], ["Waikato Region", "76,197", "39,975", "24,708", "13,161", "11,421", "12,519", "28,914"], ["Bay of Plenty Region", "50,685", "27,396", "16,296", "6,648", "7,542", "9,579", "21,501"], ["Gisborne Region", "9,570", "4,512", "2,769", "1,140", "687", "1,473", "3,072"], ["Hawke's Bay Region", "31,347", "16,005", "9,912", "4,017", "3,651", "4,830", "11,154"], ["Taranaki Region", "23,607", "11,697", "6,462", "2,424", "2,022", "3,651", "8,526"], ["Manawatu-Wanganui Region", "48,198", "23,457", "14,841", "9,060", "4,827", "7,686", "16,377"], ["Wellington Region", "64,614", "38,166", "31,344", "23,457", "17,973", "14,928", "29,679"], ["West Coast Region", "7,989", "3,570", "2,019", "780", "474", "1,080", "2,652"], ["Canterbury Region", "98,439", "55,218", "38,580", "24,960", "18,519", "14,685", "39,870"], ["Otago Region", "34,335", "18,837", "12,855", "14,787", "5,676", "6,594", "15,726"], ["Southland Region", "22,959", "11,214", "6,144", "2,163", "1,284", "2,874", "7,119"], ["Tasman Region", "8,583", "5,058", "3,303", "1,182", "1,347", "1,467", "3,984"], ["Nelson Region", "7,989", "4,437", "3,165", "1,326", "1,488", "1,596", "3,798"], ["Marlborough Region", "8,997", "4,977", "3,027", "1,233", "1,155", "1,398", "3,915"], ["Area Outside Region", "141", "54", "39", "12", "12", "18", "60"], ["Total", "708,432", "386,070", "263,847", "170,055", "172,590", "128,622", "286,599"]], "target": "0", "label": "RegionalCouncil", "table_NE": [["DATE", "ORG", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "LOC", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"]], "most_common": ["GPE", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"]}