{"filename": "C10079_C10079.csv", "header": ["Table 1: Value of U.S. Goods Trade with Canada and Mexico Compared with U.S. Merchandise Trade with All Countries: 1990–2004", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], "content": [["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Excel | CSV", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Year", "Total U.S. international merchandise trade  (Billions of current U.S. dollars)", "U.S. trade with NAFTA partners (Billions of current U.S. dollars)", "U.S. surface trade with NAFTA partners (Billions of current U.S. dollars)", "Ratio of U.S. trade with NAFTA partners to total U.S trade (Percents)", "Ratio of U.S surface trade to all U.S. trade with NAFTA partners (Percents)", "Total U.S. international merchandise trade (Billions of chained 2000 U.S. dollars)1", "U.S. trade with NAFTA partners (Billions of chained 2000 U.S. dollars)1", "U.S. surface trade with NAFTA partners (Billions of chained 2000 U.S. dollars)1"], ["1990", "889", "233", "204", "26.2", "87.5", "822", "215", "188"], ["1991", "910", "241", "210", "26.4", "87.3", "848", "224", "196"], ["1992", "981", "264", "232", "27", "87.7", "924", "249", "218"], ["1993", "1,046", "293", "258", "28", "88", "993", "278", "245"], ["1994", "1,176", "343", "312", "29.2", "90.9", "1,107", "323", "293"], ["1995", "1,328", "380", "338", "28.6", "89.1", "1,219", "349", "311"], ["1996", "1,420", "421", "377", "29.7", "89.5", "1,338", "397", "355"], ["1997", "1,560", "475", "426", "30.5", "89.6", "1,522", "464", "416"], ["1998", "1,594", "503", "452", "31.5", "89.9", "1,630", "514", "462"], ["1999", "1,720", "559", "501", "32.5", "89.7", "1,771", "575", "516"], ["2000", "2,000", "653", "576", "32.7", "88.1", "2,000", "653", "576"], ["2001", "1,870", "614", "547", "32.8", "89.2", "1,905", "625", "558"], ["2002", "1,857", "604", "541", "32.5", "89.6", "1,915", "622", "558"], ["2003", "1,983", "629", "563", "31.7", "89.4", "1,996", "633", "566"], ["2004", "2,288", "712", "634", "31.1", "89", "2,207", "687", "611"], ["Percent change,", "157.4", "205.7", "211.2", "", "", "168.3", "218.7", "224.4"], ["1990–2004", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Annual average growth rate (percents)", "7", "8.3", "8.4", "", "", "7.3", "8.6", "8.8"], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["NOTE: NAFTA = North American Free Trade Agreement", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["1 To compare economic changes over time, current or nominal values of currencies must be deflated or adjusted for inflation. In the United States, the Bureau of Economic Analysis (BEA) establishes indices to calculate changes between years. These are used to calculate real chained dollars. Annual changes in the indices are chained (multiplied) together to form a time series. Chained dollars, instead of merely reflecting inflation, capture the effect of relative changes in prices and in the composition of output. They also better reflect cyclical fluctuations in the economy. Chained 2000 dollars are the most currently available indices from BEA for adjusting for inflation.", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["SOURCE: U.S. Department of Transportation, Research and Innovative Technology Administration, Bureau of Transportation Statistics, based on: current dollars - data from the U.S. Department of Commerce, U.S. Census Bureau, Foreign Trade Division, FT920 U.S. Merchandise Trade, 1990 to 2004; chained 2000 dollars - estimates based on inflation-adjusted indices from the U.S. Department of Commerce, Bureau of Economic Analysis, National Income and Products Accounts, Tables 4.2.5 and 4.2.6, available at http://www.bea.gov/bea/dn/nipaweb/index.asp as of May 2005.", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""]], "target": "0", "label": "Year", "table_NE": [["DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "EVENT", "NORP", "GPE", "ORG", "ORG", "DATE", "DATE", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "DATE", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "DATE"], ["GPE", "GPE", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["GPE", "ORG", "GPE", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["GPE", "ORG", "GPE", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["GPE", "ORG", "GPE", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["NORP", "GPE", "ORG", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["GPE", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["GPE", "ORG", "MONEY", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["GPE", "ORG", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"]], "most_common": ["DATE", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"]}