{"filename": "C10080_C10080.csv", "header": ["Imports of services by country, 2002-2008, mill. euro", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], "content": [["Country", "Year", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "2002", "2003", "2004", "2005", "2006", "2007", "2008"], ["EU15-countries (1)", "3 200", "3 304", "3 347", "4 361", "3 915", "4 551", "6 800"], ["Netherlands", "342", "326", "360", "427", "317", "304", "357"], ["Belgium", "152", "162", "150", "144", "125", "135", "145"], ["United Kingdom", "965", "934", "859", "1 173", "1 101", "1 240", "1 459"], ["Spain", "37", "38", "49", "71", "60", "59", "81"], ["Ireland", "80", "146", "177", "202", "125", "137", "196"], ["Italy", "75", "90", "67", "74", "66", "68", "244"], ["Austria", "52", "48", "64", "57", "74", "72", "95"], ["Greece", "14", "38", "19", "29", "19", "14", "42"], ["Luxembourg", "9", "12", "10", "24", "14", "10", "13"], ["Portugal", "7", "7", "5", "9", "7", "6", "58"], ["France", "182", "181", "213", "246", "177", "182", "224"], ["Sweden", "668", "606", "620", "953", "724", "876", "870"], ["Germany", "448", "497", "561", "665", "694", "984", "2 505"], ["Denmark", "169", "219", "193", "287", "412", "464", "511"], ["Other countries (2)", "2 331", "2 413", "2 660", "3 379", "3 662", "3 984", "4 971"], ["Norway", "144", "140", "128", "179", "151", "195", "202"], ["Estonia", "57", "58", "56", "98", "92", "111", "177"], ["Russia", "194", "234", "334", "387", "267", "327", "268"], ["Switzerland", "103", "133", "154", "251", "157", "212", "289"], ["Canada", "44", "30", "45", "57", "110", "100", "133"], ["United States", "1 044", "825", "924", "986", "1 520", "1 320", "1 504"], ["Japan", "41", "34", "80", "55", "96", "77", "118"], ["China", "... 1)", "19", "77", "54", "162", "222", "363"], ["India", "... 1)", "101", "238", "374", "137", "182", "324"], ["Other", "704", "839", "624", "938", "970", "1 238", "1 593"], ["Total (1)+(2)", "5 531", "5 717", "6 007", "7 740", "7 577", "8 535", "11 771"], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Source: Foreign trade in services 2008, preliminary results, Statistics Finland", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Inquiries: Jaakko Salmela (09) 1734 2953, Marjatta Tenhunen (09) 1734 2927,globalisaatio.tilastot@stat.fi", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Director in charge: Leena Storgårds", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""]], "target": "0", "label": "Country", "table_NE": [["CARDINAL", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "CARDINAL", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "DATE", "GPE", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON"], ["DATE", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"]], "most_common": ["GPE", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"]}