{"filename": "C10082_C10082.csv", "header": ["National Center for Education Statistics", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], "content": [["Table A-1-2. Age range for compulsory school attendance and kindergarten programs, by state: Selected years,  2000–2008", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["State", "Compulsory age of attendance", "", "", "", "", "Kindergarten education, 2008", "", ""], ["", "2000", "2002", "2004", "2006", "2007", "Attendance\nrequired", "School districts\nrequired to offer", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "Half day", "Full day"], ["Alabama", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "", "", "X"], ["Alaska", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "", "", ""], ["Arizona", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "", "X", ""], ["Arkansas", "5 to 17", "5 to 17", "5 to 17", "5 to 17", "5 to 17", "X", "", "X"], ["California", "6 to 18", "6 to 18", "6 to 18", "6 to 18", "6 to 18", "", "X", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Colorado", "—", "—", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "6 to 17", "", "X", ""], ["Connecticut", "7 to 16", "7 to 18", "7 to 18", "5 to 18", "5 to 18", "X", "X", ""], ["Delaware", "5 to 16", "5 to 16", "5 to 16", "5 to 16", "5 to 16", "X", "X", "X"], ["District of Columbia", "—", "5 to 18", "5 to 18", "5 to 18", "5 to 18", "X", "X", ""], ["Florida", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "X", "X", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Georgia", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "", "", "X"], ["Hawaii", "6 to 18", "6 to 18", "6 to 18", "6 to 18", "6 to 18", "", "X", ""], ["Idaho", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "", "", ""], ["Illinois", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "7 to 17", "7 to 17", "7 to 17", "", "X", ""], ["Indiana", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "7 to 18", "7 to 18", "", "X", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Iowa", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "", "X", ""], ["Kansas", "7 to 18", "7 to 18", "7 to 18", "7 to 18", "7 to 18", "", "X", ""], ["Kentucky", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "", "X", ""], ["Louisiana", "7 to 17", "7 to 17", "7 to 17", "7 to 18", "7 to 18", "X", "", "X"], ["Maine", "7 to 17", "7 to 17", "7 to 17", "7 to 17", "7 to 17", "", "X", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Maryland", "5 to 16", "5 to 16", "5 to 16", "5 to 16", "5 to 16", "X", "", "X"], ["Massachusetts", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "", "X", ""], ["Michigan", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "", "X", ""], ["Minnesota", "7 to 18", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "", "X", ""], ["Mississippi", "6 to 17", "6 to 17", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 17", "", "", "X"], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Missouri", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "", "X", ""], ["Montana", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "", "X", ""], ["Nebraska", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "6 to 18", "6 to 18", "", "X", ""], ["Nevada", "7 to 17", "7 to 17", "7 to 17", "7 to 17", "7 to 17", "X", "X", ""], ["New Hampshire", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["New Jersey", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "", "", ""], ["New Mexico", "5 to 18", "5 to 18", "5 to 18", "5 to 18", "5 to 18", "X", "X", ""], ["New York", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "", "", ""], ["North Carolina", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "", "", "X"], ["North Dakota", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Ohio", "6 to 18", "6 to 18", "6 to 18", "6 to 18", "6 to 18", "X", "X", ""], ["Oklahoma", "5 to 18", "5 to 18", "5 to 18", "5 to 18", "5 to 18", "X", "X", "X"], ["Oregon", "7 to 18", "7 to 18", "7 to 18", "7 to 18", "7 to 18", "", "X", ""], ["Pennsylvania", "8 to 17", "8 to 17", "8 to 17", "8 to 17", "8 to 17", "", "", ""], ["Rhode Island", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "X", "X", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["South Carolina", "5 to 16", "5 to 16", "5 to 16", "5 to 17", "5 to 17", "X", "X", "X"], ["South Dakota", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "X", "X", ""], ["Tennessee", "6 to 17", "6 to 17", "6 to 17", "6 to 17", "6 to 17", "X", "X", ""], ["Texas", "6 to 18", "6 to 18", "6 to 18", "6 to 18", "6 to 18", "", "X", ""], ["Utah", "6 to 18", "6 to 18", "6 to 18", "6 to 18", "6 to 18", "", "X", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Vermont", "7 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "", "X", ""], ["Virginia", "5 to 18", "5 to 18", "5 to 18", "5 to 18", "5 to 18", "X", "X", ""], ["Washington", "8 to 17", "8 to 17", "8 to 16", "8 to 18", "8 to 18", "", "X", ""], ["West Virginia", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "X", "", "X"], ["Wisconsin", "6 to 18", "6 to 18", "6 to 18", "6 to 18", "6 to 18", "", "X", ""], ["Wyoming", "6 to 16", "6 to 16", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "7 to 16", "", "X", ""], ["X State has policy. ", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["— Not available. ", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["1 Child may be exempted from compulsory attendance if he/she meets state requirements for early withdrawal without meeting conditions for a diploma or equivalency. ", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["2 State requires either half-day or full-day program. ", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["3 Districts may apply for exemptions from the requirement for full-day kindergarten. ", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["4 Parent/guardian may request a waiver to delay entry to a later age per state law/regulation. ", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["5 Full-day requirement becomes effective upon each district’s confirming vote and upon specific funding appropriation by the General Assembly. ", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["6 Compulsory school age for all Manatee County students who turned 16 on or after October 1, 1999, is 18, except for students who earned a high school diploma prior to reaching their 18th birthday. ", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["7 State requires a “program,” not necessarily a traditional kindergarten program. ", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["8 New York City and Buffalo require school attendance until age 17 unless employed. ", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["9 Beginning in 2011–12, with the option for districts to transfer intradistrict, interdistrict, or to a licensed child care provider. ", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["SOURCE: Council of Chief State School Officers, <em>Key State Education Policies on PK–12 Education</em>, 2000, 2002, 2004, and 2006; Education Commission of the States, <em>Clearinghouse Notes</em>, August 1997; California Department of Education, Safe Schools and Violence Prevention Office, <em>School Attendance Review Boards</em>, Feb. 2001; <em>School District of Manatee County Policy and Procedures</em>, retrieved May 22, 2007, from http://www.manatee.k12.fl.us/policy_procedure/pdfs/chapters/Chapter_5.pdf; “State Kindergarten Statutes: State Comparisons,” Education Commission of the States, 2007, retrieved June 19, 2007, from http://mb2.ecs.org/reports/Report.aspx?id=14, State Notes, “State Statutes Regarding Kindergarten,” Education Commission of the States, 2008; and supplemental information from several state education websites.", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""]], "target": "0", "label": "State", "table_NE": [["CARDINAL", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "ORG", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "ORG", "CARDINAL", "GPE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "ORDINAL", "ORG", "GPE", "GPE", "DATE", "DATE", "ORG", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "ORG", "DATE", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "DATE", "ORG", "DATE", "WORK_OF_ART", "ORG", "DATE", "DATE", "WORK_OF_ART", "ORG", "DATE"], ["DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE"], ["DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE"], ["DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE"], ["DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE"], ["DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE"], ["DATE", "PERSON"], ["PERSON"], []], "most_common": ["GPE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "PERSON", "EMPTY"]}