{"filename": "C10087_C10087.csv", "header": ["TABLE 3. Top 3 States for Trade via Detroit, MI: 2008", "", "", "", ""], "content": [["", "", "", "", ""], ["($ millions)", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", ""], ["Excel | CSV", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", ""], ["Rank", "State", "Total", "Exports", "Imports"], ["1", "Michigan", "31,821", "13,583", "18,238"], ["2", "Ohio", "13,627", "9,371", "4,256"], ["3", "California", "10,724", "3,391", "7,334"], ["", "", "", "", ""], ["SOURCE: U.S. Department of Transportation, Research and Innovative Technology Administration, Bureau of Transportation Statistics, Transborder Surface Freight Data, 2008.", "", "", "", ""]], "target": "0", "label": "Rank", "table_NE": [["MONEY", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "DATE"], ["GPE", "GPE", "GPE"], ["CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL"]], "most_common": ["ORG", "GPE", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"]}