{"filename": "10s1365.xls_Data.csv", "header": ["Country", "Official Development Aid (ODA) Million U.S. dollars 2007 \\1", "Percent of Gross National Income \\2", "Percent of total Development Assistance Committee Official Development Aid \\3", "Multilateral aid Percent of Official Development Assistance 2006.0", "Grants by Non-governmental organizations \\4 Percent of Gross National Income"], "content": [["Australia", "2470.89", "0.2987033713978076", "2.3816693324686584", "15.408671734441088", "0.08551276032413603"], ["Austria", "1797.95", "0.48711450134411305", "1.7330283324275966", "27.149082706566205", "0.03712617439101262"], ["Belgium", "1953.17", "0.42653155230017314", "1.8826435373884751", "31.370556322397", "0.06339860143250937"], ["Canada", "3921.92", "0.2787231603558604", "3.7803045009674574", "31.296348573848274", "0.08773521118784852"], ["Denmark", "2563.02", "0.8073641621184667", "2.4704726363795313", "34.53347763089638", "0.026000566700984273"], ["Finland", "973.48", "0.39508160175337853", "0.9383288862602501", "45.51653883029722", "0.011898763159626416"], ["France", "9940.19", "0.38628092396086827", "9.581262493235892", "25.293120477256455", "(NA)"], ["Germany", "12290.7", "0.36685433654676647", "11.846898593046449", "32.590243617277174", "0.04597751647547293"], ["Greece", "500.82", "0.16238881528147428", "0.4827360323960004", "55.373947498761765", "0.003937030843107607"], ["Ireland", "1189.79", "0.5420278032806124", "1.1468282097049585", "38.11150480590412", "0.17922798764621833"], ["Italy", "3928.64", "0.1878953029106071", "3.7867818503898065", "45.04597536994518", "0.006671883933347068"], ["Japan", "7690.69", "0.169994665763057", "7.412989051930027", "34.62908518495013", "0.007029153497165032"], ["Luxembourg", "364.66", "0.8951079573933914", "0.3514925952907742", "29.527708025179734", "0.02369675742658966"], ["Netherlands", "6215.3", "0.8067300388830302", "5.990873491775211", "21.45176201272259", "0.040945800512882276"], ["New Zealand", "315.46", "0.2669522642368758", "0.30406914416285746", "21.596752368064955", "0.0501496670308611"], ["Norway", "3727.05", "0.9499295947729136", "3.59247100663215", "25.607208988216335", "(NA)"], ["Portugal", "470.54", "0.21960443013457784", "0.45354940434410373", "46.69357890753122", "0.0019127835868635364"], ["Spain", "5133.51", "0.36661117459534837", "4.9745430062383456", "45.14548977756334", "(NA)"], ["Sweden", "4334.08", "0.9336708474629946", "4.177581932204899", "27.8908004126464", "0.0031275724899138377"], ["Switzerland", "1680.27", "0.3654151274125022", "1.6195976062338315", "23.837491800490756", "0.09542098942589147"], ["United Kingdom", "9920.65", "0.36005159723957236", "9.562428057564357", "30.02980972821297", "0.022389488191822633"], ["United States", "21752.83", "0.157130484404571", "20.967363219489418", "10.071417219173437", "0.06815285183146177"], ["Development Assistance Committee \\3 total", "103135.61", "0.28", "100.0", "26.29838623410604", "0.042864637569354776"]], "target": "0", "label": "Country", "table_NE": [["GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "ORG"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], [], [], [], []], "most_common": ["GPE", "CARDINAL", "EMPTY", "EMPTY", "EMPTY", "EMPTY"], "related_table": ["10s1365.xls_Data.csv"], "subtable": ["0be0ebf4-84ac-4e31-83ee-412e728c82fa.xls_Institutional Ownership.csv", "3aa2b81d-aa4f-44ba-af17-e28dcb76d616.xls_Institutional Ownership.csv", "vkaminski__40930__raptor1j.xlsx_Summary.csv", "3dd4d519-d140-4901-9322-512a5126e9ee.xls_LOD.csv", "prison-population-30-sept-2016.xls_Headlines- PUBLISHED.csv", "10s1082.xls_Data.csv", "10s1172.xls_Data.csv", "10s0002.xls_Data.csv", "10s1001.xls_Data.csv", "C10132_C10132.csv", "10s1369.xls_2003-2005.csv", "C10178_C10178.csv"], "subtable-type": ["DAXAXXX", "DAXAXXX", "XWXXXX", "AAXXXA", "XAXAXXX", "IXXXAX", "PMXXXX", "AXAXX", "XAXAXXX", "PAAXXXX", "IXXXX", "IAAXXXX"], "table-type": "IAXXXX"}