{"filename": "10s0238.xls_Data.csv", "header": ["Table 238. Selected Statistics for the Largest Public School Districts: 2005-2006", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], "content": [["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["See notes", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "Number of full-", "Number of", "Number", ""], ["School district", "", "", "", "Number of", "time equivalent", "2004-05", "of schools", ""], ["", "City", "State", "County", "students \\1", "(FTE) teachers", "completers \\2", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["New York City Public Schools, New York", "New York", "NY", "New York", "1014058.0", "70888.5", "41322.0", "1408.0", ""], ["Los Angeles Unified, California", "Los Angeles", "CA", "Los Angeles", "727319.0", "34961.0", "29741.0", "808.0", ""], ["Puerto Rico Department of Education, Puerto Rico", "San Juan", "PR", "San Juan", "563490.0", "42036.0", "30371.0", "1523.0", ""], ["City of Chicago, Illinois", "Chicago", "IL", "Cook", "420982.0", "27038.5", "16866.0", "633.0", ""], ["Dade County, Florida", "Miami", "FL", "Miami-Dade", "362070.0", "20606.0", "18702.0", "394.0", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Clark County, Nevada", "Las Vegas", "NV", "Clark", "294131.0", "14862.0", "10314.0", "314.0", ""], ["Broward County, Florida", "Fort Lauderdale", "FL", "Broward", "271630.0", "15717.0", "14436.0", "285.0", ""], ["Houston Independent School District, Texas", "Houston", "TX", "Harris", "210292.0", "12081.599999999627", "8476.0", "312.0", ""], ["Hillsborough County, Florida", "Tampa", "FL", "Hillsborough", "193757.0", "10924.0", "9614.0", "261.0", ""], ["Philadelphia City School District, Pennsylvania", "Philadelphia", "PA", "Philadelphia", "184560.0", "10060.0", "10819.0", "270.0", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Hawaii Department of Education, Hawaii", "Honolulu", "HI", "Honolulu", "182818.0", "11226.0", "11014.0", "285.0", ""], ["Orange County, Florida", "Orlando", "FL", "Orange", "175609.0", "10737.0", "9434.0", "211.0", ""], ["Palm Beach County, Florida", "West Palm Beach", "FL", "Palm Beach", "174935.0", "10084.0", "9523.0", "236.0", ""], ["Fairfax County, Virginia", "Falls Church", "VA", "Fairfax", "163753.0", "13090.0", "11570.0", "207.0", ""], ["Dallas Independent School District, Texas", "Dallas", "TX", "Dallas", "161244.0", "10324.0", "6832.0", "255.0", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Gwinnett County, Georgia", "Lawrenceville", "GA", "Gwinnett", "144598.0", "9800.899999999907", "7045.0", "122.0", ""], ["Montgomery County, Maryland", "Rockville", "MD", "Montgomery", "139398.0", "9371.299999999814", "9351.0", "199.0", ""], ["Prince George's County Public Schools, Maryland", "Upper Marlboro", "MD", "Prince George's", "133325.0", "8395.299999999814", "7947.0", "205.0", ""], ["Detroit City, Michigan", "Detroit", "MI", "Wayne", "133255.0", "7187.199999999953", "5673.0", "235.0", ""], ["San Diego Unified, California", "San Diego", "CA", "San Diego", "132482.0", "7332.299999999814", "6653.0", "219.0", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Duval County, Florida", "Jacksonville", "FL", "Duval", "126662.0", "7526.0", "6276.0", "182.0", ""], ["Charlotte-Mecklenburg, North Carolina", "Charlotte", "NC", "Mecklenburg", "124005.0", "8616.0", "5836.0", "142.0", ""], ["Wake County, North Carolina", "Raleigh", "NC", "Wake", "120996.0", "8179.0", "6659.0", "138.0", ""], ["Memphis City School District, Tennessee", "Memphis", "TN", "Shelby", "120275.0", "7085.399999999907", "5946.0", "194.0", ""], ["Pinellas County, Florida", "Largo", "FL", "Pinellas", "112174.0", "6799.0", "5949.0", "173.0", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Baltimore County, Maryland", "Baltimore", "MD", "Baltimore", "107043.0", "7388.0", "7238.0", "168.0", ""], ["Cobb County, Georgia", "Marietta", "GA", "Cobb", "106724.0", "7065.199999999953", "6354.0", "110.0", ""], ["DeKalb County, Georgia", "Decatur", "GA", "De Kalb", "102310.0", "6858.299999999814", "5199.0", "148.0", ""], ["Jefferson County, Kentucky", "Louisville", "KY", "Jefferson", "98537.0", "5780.0", "5194.0", "172.0", ""], ["Albuquerque, New Mexico", "Albuquerque", "NM", "Bernalillo", "94022.0", "6138.59999999986", "4650.0", "169.0", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Long Beach Unified, California", "Long Beach", "CA", "Los Angeles", "93589.0", "4298.299999999814", "4956.0", "90.0", ""], ["Milwaukee, Wisconsin", "Milwaukee", "WI", "Milwaukee", "92395.0", "5420.299999999814", "3915.0", "235.0", ""], ["Polk County, Florida", "Bartow", "FL", "Polk", "89443.0", "6046.0", "4380.0", "153.0", ""], ["Baltimore City, Maryland", "Baltimore", "MD", "Baltimore City", "87643.0", "5666.0", "4145.0", "197.0", ""], ["Jefferson County, Colorado", "Golden", "CO", "Jefferson", "86332.0", "4784.5", "5651.0", "162.0", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Cypress-Fairbanks Independent School District, Texas", "Houston", "TX", "Harris", "86256.0", "5520.799999999814", "4622.0", "75.0", ""], ["Austin Independent School District, Texas", "Austin", "TX", "Travis", "81155.0", "5629.59999999986", "3746.0", "124.0", ""], ["Fulton County, Georgia", "Atlanta", "GA", "Fulton", "81100.0", "5634.399999999907", "4291.0", "95.0", ""], ["Fort Worth Independent School District, Texas", "Fort Worth", "TX", "Tarrant", "80336.0", "4793.59999999986", "3608.0", "147.0", ""], ["Fresno Unified, California", "Fresno", "CA", "Fresno", "79046.0", "3737.0999999999767", "4022.0", "106.0", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Northside Independent School District, TX", "San Antonio", "TX", "Bexar", "78711.0", "4866.799999999814", "4238.0", "95.0", ""], ["Jordan, UT", "Sandy", "UT", "Salt Lake", "77110.0", "3119.79999999993", "4922.0", "92.0", ""], ["Lee County School District, FL", "Fort Myers", "FL", "Lee", "75634.0", "4322.0", "3728.0", "101.0", ""], ["Brevard County, FL", "Viera", "FL", "Brevard", "75233.0", "4489.0", "4493.0", "117.0", ""], ["Mesa Unified District, AZ", "Mesa", "AZ", "Maricopa", "74626.0", "3804.79999999993", "4391.0", "89.0", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Virginia Beach City Public Schools, VA", "Virginia Beach", "VA", "Va. Beach City", "74303.0", "5647.0", "4778.0", "88.0", ""], ["Anne Arundel County, MD", "Annapolis", "MD", "Anne Arundel", "73565.0", "4754.299999999814", "4861.0", "121.0", ""], ["Nashville-Davidson, TN", "Nashville", "TN", "Davidson", "72713.0", "4950.59999999986", "3390.0", "132.0", ""], ["Denver County, CO", "Denver", "CO", "Denver", "72312.0", "3973.5999999999767", "2849.0", "148.0", ""], ["Guilford County Schools, NC", "Greensboro", "NC", "Guilford", "68951.0", "4621.0", "4087.0", "111.0", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Source: U.S. Department of Education, National Center for Education Statistics,", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Common Core of Data (CCD),  \"Local Education Agency Universe Survey,\" 2005-06,", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Version 1a.", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""]], "target": "1", "label": "City", "table_NE": [["GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "ORG", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "ORG", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "ORG", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "ORG", "GPE", "ORG", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "ORG", "GPE", "ORG", "GPE", "ORG", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "ORG", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "ORG", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "ORG", "GPE", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "DATE"], ["GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE"], ["GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE"], ["GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE"], [], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["DATE", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], []], "most_common": ["GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "EMPTY", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "EMPTY"]}