{"filename": "07tbl81or.xls_State and Other Agencies.csv", "header": ["Table 81", "", "", "", "", ""], "content": [["Full-time Law Enforcement Employees", "", "", "", "", ""], ["by State by State Agency and Other Agencies, 2007", "", "", "", "", ""], ["State", "State/Other Agency", "Unit/Office", "Total law enforcement employees", "Total officers", "Total civilians"], ["OREGONState Agencies", "Liquor Commission:", "Benton County", "1.0", "1.0", "0.0"], ["", "", "Clatsop County", "2.0", "1.0", "1.0"], ["", "", "Coos County", "2.0", "1.0", "1.0"], ["", "", "Douglas County", "2.0", "1.0", "1.0"], ["", "", "Jackson County", "7.0", "6.0", "1.0"], ["", "", "Klamath County", "1.0", "1.0", "0.0"], ["", "", "Lane County", "5.0", "4.0", "1.0"], ["", "", "Lincoln County", "2.0", "1.0", "1.0"], ["", "", "Malheur County", "1.0", "1.0", "0.0"], ["", "", "Marion County", "5.0", "4.0", "1.0"], ["", "", "Multnomah County", "22.0", "19.0", "3.0"], ["", "", "Umatilla County", "2.0", "2.0", "0.0"], ["", "", "Washington County", "2.0", "2.0", "0.0"], ["OREGONOther Agencies", "Port of Portland", "", "66.0", "53.0", "13.0"]], "target": "0", "label": "State", "table_NE": [["DATE"], ["ORG", "ORG"], ["GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"]], "most_common": ["DATE", "ORG", "GPE", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"]}