{"filename": "Table_79_Full_time_Law_Enforcement_Employees_Colorado_by_University_and_College_2017.xls_17tbl79co.csv", "header": ["Table 79", "", "", "", "", ""], "content": [["COLORADO", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Full-time Law Enforcement Employees", "", "", "", "", ""], ["by University and College, 2017", "", "", "", "", ""], ["University/College", "Campus", "Student\nenrollment1", "Total law\nenforcement \nemployees", "Total\nofficers", "Total\ncivilians"], ["Adams State University", "", "3370.0", "6.0", "5.0", "1.0"], ["Arapahoe Community College", "", "10261.0", "10.0", "8.0", "2.0"], ["Auraria Higher Education Center2", "", "", "49.0", "31.0", "18.0"], ["Colorado School of Mines", "", "6069.0", "12.0", "11.0", "1.0"], ["Colorado State University", "Fort Collins", "31856.0", "49.0", "35.0", "14.0"], ["Fort Lewis College", "", "3600.0", "10.0", "8.0", "2.0"], ["Pikes Peak Community College", "", "13154.0", "20.0", "18.0", "2.0"], ["Red Rocks Community College", "", "7738.0", "10.0", "6.0", "4.0"], ["University of Colorado:", "Boulder", "33977.0", "59.0", "34.0", "25.0"], ["", "Colorado Springs", "12559.0", "30.0", "18.0", "12.0"], ["", "Denver", "23960.0", "59.0", "26.0", "33.0"], ["University of Northern Colorado", "", "13087.0", "23.0", "15.0", "8.0"], ["1 The student enrollment figures provided by the United States Department of Education are for the 2016 school year, the most recent available. The enrollment figures include full-time and part-time students.", "", "", "", "", ""], ["2 Student enrollment figures were not available.", "", "", "", "", ""]], "target": "0", "label": "EducationalInstitution", "table_NE": [["ORG", "ORG", "DATE", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "DATE"], ["GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE"], [], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"]], "most_common": ["ORG", "GPE", "EMPTY", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"]}