{"filename": "Table_79_Full_time_Law_Enforcement_Employees_North_Dakota_by_University_and_College_2017.xls_17tbl79nd.csv", "header": ["Table 79", "", "", "", ""], "content": [["NORTH DAKOTA", "", "", "", ""], ["Full-time Law Enforcement Employees", "", "", "", ""], ["by University and College, 2017", "", "", "", ""], ["University/College", "Student\nenrollment1", "Total law\nenforcement \nemployees", "Total\nofficers", "Total\ncivilians"], ["Bismarck State College", "3976.0", "2.0", "2.0", "0.0"], ["North Dakota State College of Science", "3003.0", "4.0", "3.0", "1.0"], ["North Dakota State University", "14432.0", "24.0", "15.0", "9.0"], ["University of North Dakota", "14648.0", "17.0", "16.0", "1.0"], ["1 The student enrollment figures provided by the United States Department of Education are for the 2016 school year, the most recent available. The enrollment figures include full-time and part-time students.", "", "", "", ""]], "target": "0", "label": "EducationalInstitution", "table_NE": [["GPE", "ORG", "ORG", "DATE", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "DATE"], [], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"]], "most_common": ["ORG", "EMPTY", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"]}