{"filename": "Table_9_Offenses_Known_to_Law_Enforcement_Kansas_by_University_and_College_2017.xls_17tbl09ks.csv", "header": ["Table 9", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], "content": [["KANSAS", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Offenses Known to Law Enforcement", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["by University and College, 2017", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["University/College", "Campus", "Student\nenrollment1", "Violent\ncrime", "Murder and\nnonnegligent\nmanslaughter", "Rape2", "Robbery", "Aggravated\nassault", "Property\ncrime", "Burglary", "Larceny-\ntheft", "Motor\nvehicle\ntheft", "Arson"], ["Emporia State University", "", "5887.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "19.0", "3.0", "16.0", "0.0", "0.0"], ["Garden City Community College", "", "2053.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "8.0", "8.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0"], ["Kansas City Kansas Community College", "", "5726.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "19.0", "2.0", "15.0", "2.0", "0.0"], ["Kansas State University", "", "23779.0", "1.0", "0.0", "1.0", "0.0", "0.0", "116.0", "13.0", "101.0", "2.0", "0.0"], ["University of Kansas:", "Main Campus", "27565.0", "5.0", "0.0", "2.0", "2.0", "1.0", "152.0", "13.0", "138.0", "1.0", "0.0"], ["", "Medical Center3", "", "17.0", "0.0", "1.0", "2.0", "14.0", "119.0", "0.0", "116.0", "3.0", "0.0"], ["Washburn University", "", "6636.0", "3.0", "0.0", "2.0", "1.0", "0.0", "69.0", "2.0", "66.0", "1.0", "1.0"], ["Wichita State University", "", "14166.0", "4.0", "0.0", "1.0", "1.0", "2.0", "74.0", "5.0", "67.0", "2.0", "0.0"], ["1 The student enrollment figures provided by the United States Department of Education are for the 2016 school year, the most recent available. The enrollment figures include full-time and part-time students.", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["2 The figures shown in this column for the offense of rape were reported using only the revised Uniform Crime Reporting definition of rape. See the data declaration for further explanation.", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["3 Student enrollment figures were not available.", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["NOTE:  Caution should be exercised in making any intercampus comparisons or ranking schools because university/college crime statistics are affected by a variety of factors. These include demographic characteristics of the surrounding community, ratio of male to female students, number of on-campus residents, accessibility of the campus to outside visitors, size of enrollment, etc.", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""]], "target": "0", "label": "EducationalInstitution", "table_NE": [["GPE", "ORG", "DATE", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "DATE", "CARDINAL", "ORG", "CARDINAL"], ["FAC", "FAC"], [], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], []], "most_common": ["ORG", "FAC", "EMPTY", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "EMPTY"]}