{"filename": "07tbl08wy.xls_UCR02200-CITIES.csv", "header": ["Table 8", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], "content": [["WYOMING", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Offenses Known to Law Enforcement", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["by State by City, 2007", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["City", "Population", "Violent crime", "Murder and nonnegligent manslaughter", "Forcible rape", "Robbery", "Aggravated assault", "Property crime", "Burglary", "Larceny-theft", "Motor vehicle theft", "Arson1"], ["Afton", "1817.0", "2.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "2.0", "25.0", "10.0", "15.0", "0.0", "0.0"], ["Basin", "1242.0", "6.0", "0.0", "1.0", "0.0", "5.0", "32.0", "2.0", "30.0", "0.0", "0.0"], ["Buffalo", "4566.0", "28.0", "0.0", "2.0", "0.0", "26.0", "70.0", "6.0", "58.0", "6.0", "1.0"], ["Casper", "52434.0", "152.0", "2.0", "20.0", "22.0", "108.0", "2595.0", "504.0", "1935.0", "156.0", "7.0"], ["Cheyenne", "55604.0", "115.0", "1.0", "23.0", "13.0", "78.0", "2557.0", "261.0", "2208.0", "88.0", "11.0"], ["Cody", "9266.0", "31.0", "0.0", "3.0", "1.0", "27.0", "247.0", "37.0", "206.0", "4.0", "0.0"], ["Diamondville", "678.0", "2.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "2.0", "12.0", "3.0", "9.0", "0.0", "0.0"], ["Douglas", "5691.0", "15.0", "0.0", "2.0", "1.0", "12.0", "178.0", "20.0", "157.0", "1.0", "0.0"], ["Evanston", "11585.0", "18.0", "0.0", "7.0", "2.0", "9.0", "436.0", "44.0", "375.0", "17.0", "1.0"], ["Evansville", "2321.0", "4.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "4.0", "89.0", "11.0", "73.0", "5.0", "0.0"], ["Gillette", "24438.0", "41.0", "1.0", "9.0", "5.0", "26.0", "920.0", "103.0", "773.0", "44.0", "6.0"], ["Glenrock", "2393.0", "9.0", "0.0", "2.0", "0.0", "7.0", "45.0", "9.0", "30.0", "6.0", "0.0"], ["Green River", "11957.0", "78.0", "0.0", "2.0", "0.0", "76.0", "308.0", "55.0", "235.0", "18.0", "0.0"], ["Guernsey", "1118.0", "6.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "6.0", "11.0", "2.0", "9.0", "0.0", "1.0"], ["Hanna", "855.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "3.0", "0.0", "1.0", "2.0", "0.0"], ["Jackson", "9292.0", "42.0", "0.0", "19.0", "0.0", "23.0", "323.0", "25.0", "280.0", "18.0", "4.0"], ["Kemmerer", "2508.0", "3.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "3.0", "25.0", "1.0", "24.0", "0.0", "1.0"], ["Lander", "7066.0", "15.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "15.0", "213.0", "24.0", "178.0", "11.0", "0.0"], ["Laramie", "25504.0", "18.0", "0.0", "1.0", "4.0", "13.0", "828.0", "76.0", "690.0", "62.0", "8.0"], ["Lovell", "2279.0", "4.0", "1.0", "0.0", "0.0", "3.0", "28.0", "0.0", "28.0", "0.0", "0.0"], ["Lusk", "1316.0", "5.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "5.0", "17.0", "4.0", "13.0", "0.0", "0.0"], ["Mills", "2926.0", "9.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "9.0", "87.0", "13.0", "68.0", "6.0", "1.0"], ["Moorcroft", "861.0", "1.0", "0.0", "0.0", "1.0", "0.0", "14.0", "8.0", "5.0", "1.0", "0.0"], ["Newcastle", "3275.0", "12.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "12.0", "122.0", "19.0", "96.0", "7.0", "0.0"], ["Pine Bluffs", "1142.0", "5.0", "0.0", "1.0", "0.0", "4.0", "20.0", "6.0", "13.0", "1.0", "0.0"], ["Powell", "5388.0", "11.0", "0.0", "4.0", "0.0", "7.0", "202.0", "17.0", "179.0", "6.0", "3.0"], ["Rawlins", "8572.0", "54.0", "1.0", "5.0", "3.0", "45.0", "377.0", "53.0", "307.0", "17.0", "1.0"], ["Riverton", "9795.0", "32.0", "0.0", "7.0", "1.0", "24.0", "417.0", "49.0", "337.0", "31.0", "2.0"], ["Rock Springs", "19432.0", "135.0", "3.0", "9.0", "16.0", "107.0", "851.0", "154.0", "643.0", "54.0", "6.0"], ["Saratoga", "1721.0", "1.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "1.0", "22.0", "0.0", "22.0", "0.0", "0.0"], ["Sheridan", "16507.0", "9.0", "0.0", "2.0", "3.0", "4.0", "372.0", "58.0", "297.0", "17.0", "4.0"], ["Sundance", "1199.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "12.0", "4.0", "7.0", "1.0", "0.0"], ["Thermopolis", "2912.0", "17.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "17.0", "81.0", "10.0", "70.0", "1.0", "0.0"], ["Torrington", "5446.0", "7.0", "0.0", "0.0", "1.0", "6.0", "170.0", "36.0", "133.0", "1.0", "0.0"], ["Wheatland", "3426.0", "7.0", "0.0", "1.0", "0.0", "6.0", "121.0", "17.0", "100.0", "4.0", "1.0"], ["Worland", "4857.0", "15.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "15.0", "43.0", "10.0", "25.0", "8.0", "0.0"], ["1 The FBI does not publish arson data unless it receives data from either the agency or the state for all 12 months of the calendar year.", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""]], "target": "0", "label": "City", "table_NE": [["DATE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "ORG", "DATE"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"]], "most_common": ["GPE", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"]}