{"filename": "07tbl10ar.xls_Sheet1.csv", "header": ["Table 10", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], "content": [["ARKANSAS", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Offenses Known to Law Enforcement", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["by State by Metropolitan and Nonmetropolitan Counties, 2007", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["[The data shown in this table do not reflect county totals but are the number of offenses reported by the sheriff's office or county police department.]", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["Metropolitan/Nonmetropolitan Counties", "County", "Violent crime", "Murder and nonnegligent manslaughter", "Forcible rape", "Robbery", "Aggravated assault", "Property crime", "Burglary", "Larceny-theft", "Motor vehicle theft", "Arson1"], ["Metropolitan Counties", "Cleveland", "2.0", "0.0", "0.0", "1.0", "1.0", "101.0", "49.0", "42.0", "10.0", "1.0"], ["", "Craighead", "22.0", "0.0", "4.0", "1.0", "17.0", "373.0", "135.0", "211.0", "27.0", "5.0"], ["", "Crittenden", "81.0", "2.0", "8.0", "7.0", "64.0", "465.0", "178.0", "256.0", "31.0", "11.0"], ["", "Faulkner", "44.0", "0.0", "2.0", "2.0", "40.0", "745.0", "162.0", "526.0", "57.0", "5.0"], ["", "Franklin", "21.0", "0.0", "2.0", "0.0", "19.0", "181.0", "63.0", "107.0", "11.0", "5.0"], ["", "Garland", "96.0", "3.0", "14.0", "7.0", "72.0", "2306.0", "936.0", "1196.0", "174.0", "3.0"], ["", "Grant", "38.0", "0.0", "5.0", "1.0", "32.0", "178.0", "63.0", "103.0", "12.0", "0.0"], ["", "Jefferson", "69.0", "3.0", "7.0", "9.0", "50.0", "489.0", "202.0", "225.0", "62.0", "5.0"], ["", "Lincoln", "18.0", "0.0", "3.0", "0.0", "15.0", "83.0", "45.0", "38.0", "0.0", "0.0"], ["", "Lonoke", "122.0", "5.0", "12.0", "4.0", "101.0", "616.0", "209.0", "339.0", "68.0", "5.0"], ["", "Madison", "30.0", "1.0", "5.0", "0.0", "24.0", "61.0", "24.0", "31.0", "6.0", "4.0"], ["", "Perry", "14.0", "0.0", "1.0", "0.0", "13.0", "64.0", "41.0", "21.0", "2.0", "3.0"], ["", "Poinsett", "66.0", "0.0", "3.0", "2.0", "61.0", "112.0", "103.0", "4.0", "5.0", "6.0"], ["", "Pulaski", "402.0", "4.0", "17.0", "36.0", "345.0", "2223.0", "898.0", "1056.0", "269.0", "11.0"], ["", "Saline", "95.0", "0.0", "10.0", "5.0", "80.0", "1016.0", "315.0", "645.0", "56.0", "3.0"], ["", "Sebastian", "66.0", "1.0", "6.0", "5.0", "54.0", "413.0", "150.0", "243.0", "20.0", "2.0"], ["", "Washington", "142.0", "1.0", "24.0", "4.0", "113.0", "657.0", "259.0", "354.0", "44.0", "4.0"], ["Nonmetropolitan Counties", "Arkansas", "7.0", "0.0", "1.0", "0.0", "6.0", "90.0", "32.0", "47.0", "11.0", "1.0"], ["", "Ashley", "12.0", "0.0", "2.0", "0.0", "10.0", "149.0", "53.0", "86.0", "10.0", "0.0"], ["", "Baxter", "31.0", "1.0", "0.0", "1.0", "29.0", "613.0", "112.0", "464.0", "37.0", "6.0"], ["", "Boone", "42.0", "2.0", "12.0", "0.0", "28.0", "301.0", "98.0", "171.0", "32.0", "4.0"], ["", "Bradley", "4.0", "0.0", "1.0", "0.0", "3.0", "18.0", "10.0", "4.0", "4.0", "0.0"], ["", "Calhoun", "1.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "1.0", "23.0", "15.0", "5.0", "3.0", "0.0"], ["", "Carroll", "27.0", "0.0", "2.0", "0.0", "25.0", "225.0", "53.0", "155.0", "17.0", "6.0"], ["", "Chicot", "6.0", "1.0", "1.0", "0.0", "4.0", "80.0", "7.0", "58.0", "15.0", "0.0"], ["", "Clark", "18.0", "0.0", "2.0", "0.0", "16.0", "171.0", "87.0", "72.0", "12.0", "1.0"], ["", "Clay", "12.0", "0.0", "2.0", "0.0", "10.0", "90.0", "31.0", "56.0", "3.0", "0.0"], ["", "Cleburne", "50.0", "1.0", "6.0", "1.0", "42.0", "376.0", "175.0", "170.0", "31.0", "2.0"], ["", "Columbia", "30.0", "0.0", "2.0", "3.0", "25.0", "199.0", "60.0", "132.0", "7.0", "0.0"], ["", "Cross", "35.0", "0.0", "1.0", "1.0", "33.0", "214.0", "41.0", "164.0", "9.0", "0.0"], ["", "Dallas", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "23.0", "5.0", "18.0", "0.0", "0.0"], ["", "Drew", "35.0", "1.0", "1.0", "0.0", "33.0", "133.0", "44.0", "75.0", "14.0", "1.0"], ["", "Fulton", "11.0", "0.0", "1.0", "0.0", "10.0", "77.0", "38.0", "38.0", "1.0", "0.0"], ["", "Greene", "15.0", "0.0", "3.0", "0.0", "12.0", "203.0", "90.0", "106.0", "7.0", "4.0"], ["", "Hempstead", "26.0", "0.0", "5.0", "1.0", "20.0", "139.0", "52.0", "74.0", "13.0", "1.0"], ["", "Howard", "8.0", "0.0", "3.0", "0.0", "5.0", "107.0", "51.0", "56.0", "0.0", "0.0"], ["", "Independence", "101.0", "2.0", "13.0", "6.0", "80.0", "1258.0", "431.0", "745.0", "82.0", "13.0"], ["", "Izard", "12.0", "0.0", "0.0", "2.0", "10.0", "100.0", "52.0", "39.0", "9.0", "4.0"], ["", "Jackson", "25.0", "0.0", "7.0", "0.0", "18.0", "164.0", "55.0", "93.0", "16.0", "2.0"], ["", "Johnson", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "120.0", "27.0", "89.0", "4.0", "0.0"], ["", "Lafayette", "5.0", "0.0", "0.0", "1.0", "4.0", "60.0", "55.0", "2.0", "3.0", "0.0"], ["", "Lawrence", "26.0", "0.0", "2.0", "0.0", "24.0", "164.0", "85.0", "79.0", "0.0", "1.0"], ["", "Lee", "16.0", "5.0", "1.0", "0.0", "10.0", "14.0", "10.0", "4.0", "0.0", "0.0"], ["", "Little River", "2.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "2.0", "33.0", "7.0", "23.0", "3.0", "1.0"], ["", "Logan", "18.0", "0.0", "6.0", "1.0", "11.0", "258.0", "91.0", "145.0", "22.0", "5.0"], ["", "Marion", "41.0", "0.0", "3.0", "0.0", "38.0", "169.0", "44.0", "122.0", "3.0", "3.0"], ["", "Mississippi", "43.0", "0.0", "8.0", "5.0", "30.0", "400.0", "99.0", "254.0", "47.0", "4.0"], ["", "Monroe", "2.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "2.0", "58.0", "16.0", "26.0", "16.0", "1.0"], ["", "Montgomery2", "", "0.0", "3.0", "0.0", "", "157.0", "38.0", "104.0", "15.0", "0.0"], ["", "Nevada", "16.0", "2.0", "1.0", "1.0", "12.0", "32.0", "13.0", "17.0", "2.0", "0.0"], ["", "Ouachita", "29.0", "1.0", "2.0", "5.0", "21.0", "215.0", "87.0", "106.0", "22.0", "2.0"], ["", "Polk", "31.0", "0.0", "1.0", "2.0", "28.0", "154.0", "66.0", "77.0", "11.0", "1.0"], ["", "Pope", "42.0", "0.0", "9.0", "0.0", "33.0", "378.0", "140.0", "209.0", "29.0", "3.0"], ["", "Randolph", "7.0", "0.0", "3.0", "0.0", "4.0", "12.0", "5.0", "7.0", "0.0", "1.0"], ["", "Scott", "6.0", "0.0", "4.0", "0.0", "2.0", "67.0", "33.0", "32.0", "2.0", "1.0"], ["", "Searcy", "1.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "1.0", "15.0", "11.0", "3.0", "1.0", "0.0"], ["", "Sevier", "14.0", "0.0", "3.0", "2.0", "9.0", "144.0", "58.0", "81.0", "5.0", "1.0"], ["", "St. Francis", "40.0", "1.0", "2.0", "12.0", "25.0", "401.0", "129.0", "271.0", "1.0", "2.0"], ["", "Stone", "3.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "3.0", "31.0", "13.0", "16.0", "2.0", "1.0"], ["", "Union", "25.0", "0.0", "1.0", "6.0", "18.0", "421.0", "68.0", "313.0", "40.0", "3.0"], ["", "Van Buren", "21.0", "0.0", "1.0", "0.0", "20.0", "124.0", "26.0", "80.0", "18.0", "0.0"], ["", "White", "62.0", "0.0", "14.0", "3.0", "45.0", "789.0", "285.0", "420.0", "84.0", "4.0"], ["", "Woodruff", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "0.0", "14.0", "1.0", "10.0", "3.0", "0.0"], ["", "Yell", "52.0", "0.0", "3.0", "1.0", "48.0", "116.0", "71.0", "27.0", "18.0", "6.0"], ["1 The FBI does not publish arson data unless it receives data from either the agency or the state for all 12 months of the calendar year.", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["2  It was determined that the agency did not follow national Uniform Crime Reporting (UCR) Program guidelines for reporting an offense.  Consequently, this figure is not included in this table.", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", "", ""]], "target": "1", "label": "County", "table_NE": [["LOC", "DATE", "GPE", "LOC", "ORG", "DATE", "ORG"], ["PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "GPE", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "GPE", "PERSON", "PERSON", "GPE", "PERSON", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "GPE", "PERSON", "GPE", "GPE", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"]], "most_common": ["LOC", "PERSON", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"]}