{"filename": "ClinicProjects.xls_Civil and Environmental.csv", "header": ["Proj #", "Project Title", "PM", "Co-PM's", "Project Identifier Name", "Students - Fall 2002", "Funding Source", "CEE", "ChE", "ME", "ECE", "Total"], "content": [["CE-01", "Modeling of Autotrophic Denitrification Kinetics", "Jahan", "", "Kinetics", "Kline, Johanna (ChE)", "NJ Seagrant", "", "1.0", "", "", "1.0"], ["CE-02", "Field Methods", "Jahan", "Everett", "Field Methods", "Diglio, Stephen; Magill, Matthew; Michiels, Joseph", "NSF", "3.0", "", "", "", "3.0"], ["CE-03", "Automated Detection and Identification of Odors Using an Electronic Nose System", "Jahan", "Polikar", "Nose", "Wittohn, Paul; Hugette Mualem (ChE); Mike Faith (ECE)", "NATC", "2.0", "1.0", "", "1.0", "4.0"], ["CE-04", "Site Remediation", "Everett", "", "Remediation", "Snyder, Dale; Craig Agin; Winn, Kelly; Don DeFeo (ChE); Desiree D'Orazio (ME)", "DOE/AFCEE/SJGas", "3.0", "1.0", "1.0", "", "5.0"], ["CE-05", "Civil City - Virtual City for Engineers", "Everett", "Entire CEE dept.", "Civil City", "Smith, Brad; Patrick Violante (ECE); Will Kim (ECE)", "NSF", "1.0", "", "", "2.0", "3.0"], ["CE-06", "Chestnut Branch Stream Restoration", "Orlins", "", "Chestnut Branch", "Fargnoli, Thomas; Nastasi, Laura; Newton, Doug; Chris Williams (ECE)", "Glou. Co. & DEP", "3.0", "", "", "1.0", "4.0"], ["CE-07", "Lake Kandle Dam Analysis", "Orlins", "", "Kandle Dam", "Oman, Clint; Ross, Sarah; Lisa Petronis (ME)", "EarthSolve, Kandle Land Assoc.", "2.0", "", "1.0", "", "3.0"], ["CE-08", "DRPA Bridge Soil Modeling", "Sukumaran", "Dusseau, Cleary", "Soil Modeling", "D'Alessandro, Michele; Gerber, Aaron; Terry, Caitlin; Dan Smith (ME)", "DRPA", "3.0", "", "1.0", "", "4.0"], ["CE-9", "FAA flexible pavement analysis", "Sukumaran", "", "Pavement", "Willis, Michael; Diane Barclay (ME); Rabon Jones (ME)", "FAA", "1.0", "", "2.0", "", "3.0"], ["CE-10", "DRBA/DRPA Bridge Field Measurements", "Dusseau", "Ravi, Cleary, Sukumaran", "DRPA Field", "Dan Marks (ECE)", "DRBA and DRPA", "", "", "", "1.0", "1.0"], ["CE-11", "Anchorage of rebar in fiber reinforced concrete", "Cleary", "", "Rebar", "MacBrair, Gerald; Moore, Scott; Tortorice, Rosie", "Internal from unspent CIAP funds", "3.0", "", "", "", "3.0"], ["CE-12", "DRPA Bridge Structure Modeling and DRBA/DRPA Bridge Field Measurements", "Cleary", "Dusseau", "Structure Modeling", "Wittohn, John; Huynh-Ba, Gia; Daniel Marks (ECE)", "DRPA", "2.0", "", "", "1.0", "3.0"], ["CE-13", "Constructibility Issues Animations", "Cleary", "Dr. Philpot (UM- Rolla)", "Constructability", "Bush, Stacey; Gallagher, Katheryn", "CIAP", "2.0", "", "", "", "2.0"], ["CE-14", "Investigating New Devices for Determining Mechanical Properties of Asphalt Concrete", "Mehta", "Sukumaran", "Asphalt", "Weaver, Joseph; Merla, Nunzio", "WisDOT", "2.0", "", "", "", "2.0"], ["CE-15", "Evaluation of Rubber as a Recycled Material", "Mehta", "", "Rubber", "Laicovsky, Jim; Miller, Laura; Mandy Zimerman (ME)", "Internal", "2.0", "", "1.0", "", "3.0"], ["ChE-09", "Diesel Emission", "Hesketh", "Marchese, Slater", "School Bus", "Fusaro, Jessica", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["ChE-13", "Modeling Polymers", "Newell", "", "Kevlar", "Mattson, Crystal", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["ECE-11", "Streetlight Lamps", "Jansson", "Schmalzel", "Street lamps", "Steinberg, Brett", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["ECE-12", "Strategic&BusPlan", "Jansson", "", "Business", "Zeleznock, Andrew", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["ME-03", "Human Powrd Stair Climber", "Chandrupatla", "Constans, Marchese", "Stair Climber", "Lewis, Philip", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["ME-05", "RSD Helicopter Lndng", "Chandrupatla", "", "Helicopter", "Williams, Courtney", "", "", "", "", "", ""], ["ME-06", "Fire Hose Fracture", "Chen", "Marchese", "Fir Hose", "Volturo, Lea", "", "", "", "", "", ""]], "target": "11", "label": "Total", "table_NE": [["DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE"], ["EVENT", "LOC", "ORG", "ORG"], ["PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON"], ["PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON"], ["LOC", "FAC"], ["PERSON", "PERSON", "ORG", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "ORG", "PERSON", "ORG", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "ORG", "PERSON", "ORG", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "ORG", "PERSON", "ORG", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "ORG", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "ORG", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "ORG", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "ORG", "PERSON", "ORG", "PERSON", "ORG", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "ORG", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "ORG", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON"], ["ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"]], "most_common": ["DATE2", "ORG", "PERSON2", "PERSON2", "LOC", "PERSON2", "ORG", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], "related_table": ["ClinicProjects.xls_Civil and Environmental.csv"], "subtable": [], "subtable-type": [], "table-type": "CPSSLSPAAAAA"}