{"filename": "Table_80_Full_time_Law_Enforcement_Employees_Louisiana_by_Metropolitan_and_Nonmetropolitan_Counties_2017.xls_17tbl80la.csv", "header": ["Metropolitan/Nonmetropolitan", "County", "Total law\nenforcement\nemployees", "Total\nofficers", "Total\ncivilians"], "content": [["Metropolitan Counties", "Acadia", "99.0", "57.0", "42.0"], ["", "Ascension", "329.0", "274.0", "55.0"], ["", "Bossier", "379.0", "308.0", "71.0"], ["", "Caddo", "686.0", "413.0", "273.0"], ["", "Calcasieu", "831.0", "831.0", "0.0"], ["", "De Soto", "113.0", "103.0", "10.0"], ["", "East Baton Rouge", "827.0", "706.0", "121.0"], ["", "East Feliciana", "54.0", "54.0", "0.0"], ["", "Grant", "73.0", "61.0", "12.0"], ["", "Iberia", "254.0", "172.0", "82.0"], ["", "Jefferson", "1458.0", "1000.0", "458.0"], ["", "Lafayette", "769.0", "600.0", "169.0"], ["", "Lafourche", "331.0", "276.0", "55.0"], ["", "Livingston", "283.0", "283.0", "0.0"], ["", "Ouachita", "396.0", "396.0", "0.0"], ["", "Plaquemines", "228.0", "228.0", "0.0"], ["", "Pointe Coupee", "104.0", "56.0", "48.0"], ["", "St. Bernard", "270.0", "248.0", "22.0"], ["", "St. Charles", "382.0", "212.0", "170.0"], ["", "St. Helena", "42.0", "26.0", "16.0"], ["", "St. James", "100.0", "60.0", "40.0"], ["", "St. John the Baptist", "240.0", "239.0", "1.0"], ["", "St. Martin", "170.0", "118.0", "52.0"], ["", "St. Tammany", "661.0", "498.0", "163.0"], ["", "Tangipahoa", "241.0", "115.0", "126.0"], ["", "Terrebonne", "308.0", "240.0", "68.0"], ["", "Union", "48.0", "32.0", "16.0"], ["", "Vermilion", "145.0", "119.0", "26.0"], ["", "Webster", "128.0", "107.0", "21.0"], ["", "West Baton Rouge", "183.0", "140.0", "43.0"], ["", "West Feliciana", "69.0", "69.0", "0.0"], ["Nonmetropolitan Counties", "Allen", "82.0", "82.0", "0.0"], ["", "Assumption", "83.0", "53.0", "30.0"], ["", "Avoyelles", "92.0", "62.0", "30.0"], ["", "Beauregard", "87.0", "68.0", "19.0"], ["", "Bienville", "70.0", "42.0", "28.0"], ["", "Catahoula", "107.0", "31.0", "76.0"], ["", "Claiborne", "87.0", "38.0", "49.0"], ["", "Concordia", "232.0", "24.0", "208.0"], ["", "East Carroll", "41.0", "14.0", "27.0"], ["", "Evangeline", "32.0", "25.0", "7.0"], ["", "Franklin", "129.0", "129.0", "0.0"], ["", "Jackson", "180.0", "44.0", "136.0"], ["", "Jefferson Davis", "77.0", "77.0", "0.0"], ["", "La Salle", "49.0", "31.0", "18.0"], ["", "Lincoln", "79.0", "56.0", "23.0"], ["", "Madison", "34.0", "34.0", "0.0"], ["", "Morehouse", "130.0", "130.0", "0.0"], ["", "Natchitoches", "196.0", "160.0", "36.0"], ["", "Richland", "136.0", "116.0", "20.0"], ["", "Sabine", "86.0", "63.0", "23.0"], ["", "St. Landry", "201.0", "90.0", "111.0"], ["", "St. Mary", "150.0", "150.0", "0.0"], ["", "Vernon", "163.0", "66.0", "97.0"], ["", "Washington", "79.0", "62.0", "17.0"], ["", "West Carroll", "20.0", "10.0", "10.0"]], "target": "1", "label": "County", "table_NE": [[], ["ORG", "ORG", "GPE", "ORG", "ORG", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "GPE", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "GPE", "GPE", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "GPE", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "ORG", "GPE", "GPE", "ORG", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE", "GPE"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"]], "most_common": ["EMPTY", "ORG", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], "related_table": ["Table_80_Full_time_Law_Enforcement_Employees_Louisiana_by_Metropolitan_and_Nonmetropolitan_Counties_2017.xls_17tbl80la.csv"], "subtable": ["Table_78_Full_time_Law_Enforcement_Employees_Delaware_by_Cities_2017.xls_17tbl78de.csv", "Motor_Vehicle_Theft_Table_Motor_Vehicle_Theft_Percent_Distribution_by_Region_2017.xls_17mvttbl.csv", "07tbl78de.xls_Sheet1.csv", "Expanded_Homicide_Data_Table_4_Murder_by_Victim_Offender_Situations_2017.xls_17shrtbl04.csv", "07tbl78nh.xls_Sheet1.csv", "07tbl78nc.xls_Sheet1.csv", "Table_78_Full_time_Law_Enforcement_Employees_North_Dakota_by_Cities_2017.xls_17tbl78nd.csv", "07tbl78mn.xls_Sheet1.csv", "07mvttbl.xls_Sheet1.csv", "Table_79_Full_time_Law_Enforcement_Employees_North_Dakota_by_University_and_College_2017.xls_17tbl79nd.csv", "07tbl79nc.xls_Sheet1.csv", "07tbl78co.xls_Sheet1.csv", "Expanded_Homicide_Data_Table_1_Murder_Victims_by_Race_Ethnicity_and_Sex_2017.xls_17shrtbl01.csv", "david_delainey__8083__ENA Status of Completed Reviews.xlsx_Sheet1.csv", "0b62ac60-cc3a-46c9-a261-e0059011ad68.xlsx_Charter Schools.csv", "0b62ac60-cc3a-46c9-a261-e0059011ad68.xlsx_School Districts.csv", "3aa2b81d-aa4f-44ba-af17-e28dcb76d616.xls_Insider Ownership.csv", "0c79b9a8-fb2f-4909-9abd-067130a9002f.xlsx_2010.csv", "0c79b9a8-fb2f-4909-9abd-067130a9002f.xlsx_2004.csv", "0be0ebf4-84ac-4e31-83ee-412e728c82fa.xls_Insider Ownership.csv", "0c79b9a8-fb2f-4909-9abd-067130a9002f.xlsx_2007.csv", "0c79b9a8-fb2f-4909-9abd-067130a9002f.xlsx_2001.csv", "0c79b9a8-fb2f-4909-9abd-067130a9002f.xlsx_2003.csv", "0c79b9a8-fb2f-4909-9abd-067130a9002f.xlsx_2009.csv", "6a193820-fef7-44ac-9d86-4fcbe38e65eb.xls_Insider Ownership.csv", "0c79b9a8-fb2f-4909-9abd-067130a9002f.xlsx_2008.csv", "0c79b9a8-fb2f-4909-9abd-067130a9002f.xlsx_2002.csv", "0c79b9a8-fb2f-4909-9abd-067130a9002f.xlsx_2006.csv", "0c79b9a8-fb2f-4909-9abd-067130a9002f.xlsx_2005.csv", "HIL 2015 tables - no charts.xls_4.6 Median price by MSOA.csv", "SC SF1 Air pollution.xlsx_SC SF1 Air Pollution.csv", "Report 1748 & Background DataV1.xlsx_Table 5.4.csv", "main-tables.xls_2.4.csv", "2csj3h29fr-1.zip_full_table_202004060334-TCNJ6C9A7M6N71CB_GIGMd_Trinity_Assembly.tsv.csv", "10s0007.xls_2000, April (Estimates Base).csv", "10s0007.xls_2005.csv", "10s0007.xls_2006.csv", "10s0007.xls_2007.csv", "10s0007.xls_2004.csv", "10s0070.xls_Data.csv", "C10093_C10093.csv", "C10159_C10159.csv", "C10020_C10020.csv", "C10087_C10087.csv", "C10044_C10044.csv", "C10096_C10096.csv", "C10142_C10142.csv", "C10062_C10062.csv", "C10013_C10013.csv", "07tbl81pa.xls_State and Other Agencies.csv", "07tbl80mo.xls_Sheet1.csv", "Table_81_Full_time_Law_Enforcement_Employees_Missouri_by_State_Tribal_and_Other_Agencies_2017.xls_17tbl81mo.csv", "Table_81_Full_time_Law_Enforcement_Employees_West_Virginia_by_State_Tribal_and_Other_Agencies_2017.xls_17tbl81wv.csv", "Table_80_Full_time_Law_Enforcement_Employees_North_Dakota_by_Metropolitan_and_Nonmetropolitan_Counties_2017.xls_17tbl80nd.csv", "07tbl81or.xls_State and Other Agencies.csv", "07tbl80fl.xls_Sheet1.csv", "Report 1652 & Background Data_Final.xls_Table 5.1.csv", "C10051_C10051.csv", "C10179_C10179.csv"], "subtable-type": ["IAAAA", "LAAAA", "XIAAAA", "XAA", "XIAAAA", "XIAAAA", "IAAAA", "XIAAAA", "LAAAA", "PXAAA", "XPIAAAA", "XIAAAA", "NAAAA", "PSAAA", "APAA", "APAA", "DAAA", "APAXA", "APAXA", "DAAA", "APAXA", "APAXA", "APAXA", "APAXA", "DAAA", "APAXA", "APAXA", "APAXA", "APAXA", "XIIAA", "IAAA", "AXAAAA", "XAAAXA", "XXXAA", "CAAAA", "CAAAA", "CAAAA", "CAAAA", "CAAAA", "NXAAAA", "AAA", "XAAAAA", "PAAAA", "AIAAA", "IAAAA", "WAAAA", "BAAAA", "AIAAA", "AIAAA", "XPIAAA", "XSAAA", "XPPAAA", "XPIAAA", "XSAAA", "XPIAAA", "XIAAA", "XXAAA", "XAAAA", "XAAAA"], "table-type": "XPAAA"}