{"filename": "Table_80_Full_time_Law_Enforcement_Employees_North_Dakota_by_Metropolitan_and_Nonmetropolitan_Counties_2017.xls_17tbl80nd.csv", "header": ["Metropolitan/Nonmetropolitan", "County", "Total law\nenforcement\nemployees", "Total\nofficers", "Total\ncivilians"], "content": [["Metropolitan Counties", "Burleigh", "64.0", "52.0", "12.0"], ["", "Cass", "166.0", "105.0", "61.0"], ["", "Grand Forks", "39.0", "33.0", "6.0"], ["", "Morton", "44.0", "35.0", "9.0"], ["", "Oliver", "5.0", "4.0", "1.0"], ["", "Sioux", "1.0", "1.0", "0.0"], ["Nonmetropolitan Counties", "Adams", "6.0", "6.0", "0.0"], ["", "Barnes", "9.0", "8.0", "1.0"], ["", "Benson", "4.0", "4.0", "0.0"], ["", "Billings", "6.0", "6.0", "0.0"], ["", "Bottineau", "20.0", "11.0", "9.0"], ["", "Bowman", "5.0", "4.0", "1.0"], ["", "Burke", "5.0", "4.0", "1.0"], ["", "Cavalier", "12.0", "6.0", "6.0"], ["", "Dickey", "5.0", "4.0", "1.0"], ["", "Divide", "6.0", "6.0", "0.0"], ["", "Dunn", "17.0", "15.0", "2.0"], ["", "Eddy", "5.0", "4.0", "1.0"], ["", "Emmons", "6.0", "5.0", "1.0"], ["", "Foster", "2.0", "2.0", "0.0"], ["", "Golden Valley", "5.0", "4.0", "1.0"], ["", "Grant", "4.0", "4.0", "0.0"], ["", "Griggs", "3.0", "3.0", "0.0"], ["", "Hettinger", "6.0", "5.0", "1.0"], ["", "Kidder", "4.0", "3.0", "1.0"], ["", "Lamoure", "6.0", "5.0", "1.0"], ["", "Logan", "3.0", "3.0", "0.0"], ["", "McHenry", "8.0", "8.0", "0.0"], ["", "McIntosh", "3.0", "3.0", "0.0"], ["", "McKenzie", "49.0", "30.0", "19.0"], ["", "McLean", "42.0", "25.0", "17.0"], ["", "Mercer", "30.0", "22.0", "8.0"], ["", "Mountrail", "24.0", "12.0", "12.0"], ["", "Nelson", "6.0", "5.0", "1.0"], ["", "Pembina", "16.0", "9.0", "7.0"], ["", "Pierce", "37.0", "3.0", "34.0"], ["", "Ramsey", "8.0", "7.0", "1.0"], ["", "Ransom", "5.0", "4.0", "1.0"], ["", "Renville", "6.0", "6.0", "0.0"], ["", "Richland", "35.0", "18.0", "17.0"], ["", "Rolette", "16.0", "6.0", "10.0"], ["", "Sargent", "6.0", "5.0", "1.0"], ["", "Sheridan", "3.0", "3.0", "0.0"], ["", "Slope", "2.0", "2.0", "0.0"], ["", "Stark", "30.0", "25.0", "5.0"], ["", "Steele", "3.0", "3.0", "0.0"], ["", "Stutsman", "33.0", "13.0", "20.0"], ["", "Towner", "6.0", "5.0", "1.0"], ["", "Traill", "13.0", "8.0", "5.0"], ["", "Walsh", "18.0", "11.0", "7.0"], ["", "Ward", "90.0", "35.0", "55.0"], ["", "Wells", "4.0", "3.0", "1.0"], ["", "Williams", "75.0", "37.0", "38.0"]], "target": "1", "label": "County", "table_NE": [[], ["PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "GPE", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], ["CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"]], "most_common": ["EMPTY", "PERSON2", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL", "CARDINAL"], "related_table": ["Table_80_Full_time_Law_Enforcement_Employees_North_Dakota_by_Metropolitan_and_Nonmetropolitan_Counties_2017.xls_17tbl80nd.csv", "07tbl80mo.xls_Sheet1.csv"], "subtable": ["Table_78_Full_time_Law_Enforcement_Employees_Delaware_by_Cities_2017.xls_17tbl78de.csv", "07tbl81pa.xls_State and Other Agencies.csv", "Motor_Vehicle_Theft_Table_Motor_Vehicle_Theft_Percent_Distribution_by_Region_2017.xls_17mvttbl.csv", "07tbl78de.xls_Sheet1.csv", "Expanded_Homicide_Data_Table_4_Murder_by_Victim_Offender_Situations_2017.xls_17shrtbl04.csv", "07tbl78nh.xls_Sheet1.csv", "Table_81_Full_time_Law_Enforcement_Employees_Missouri_by_State_Tribal_and_Other_Agencies_2017.xls_17tbl81mo.csv", "07tbl78nc.xls_Sheet1.csv", "Table_78_Full_time_Law_Enforcement_Employees_North_Dakota_by_Cities_2017.xls_17tbl78nd.csv", "Table_81_Full_time_Law_Enforcement_Employees_West_Virginia_by_State_Tribal_and_Other_Agencies_2017.xls_17tbl81wv.csv", "07tbl78mn.xls_Sheet1.csv", "07mvttbl.xls_Sheet1.csv", "Table_79_Full_time_Law_Enforcement_Employees_North_Dakota_by_University_and_College_2017.xls_17tbl79nd.csv", "07tbl81or.xls_State and Other Agencies.csv", "07tbl78co.xls_Sheet1.csv", "Expanded_Homicide_Data_Table_1_Murder_Victims_by_Race_Ethnicity_and_Sex_2017.xls_17shrtbl01.csv", "0c69b9ea-0f6a-41d7-bcde-246e199f2a1c.xlsx_ISH.csv", "1d2e5c61-588e-44df-8885-16a2e3d7e52b.xls_Proteins.csv", "3aa2b81d-aa4f-44ba-af17-e28dcb76d616.xls_Insider Ownership.csv", "0be0ebf4-84ac-4e31-83ee-412e728c82fa.xls_Insider Ownership.csv", "6a193820-fef7-44ac-9d86-4fcbe38e65eb.xls_Insider Ownership.csv", "HIL 2015 tables - no charts.xls_4.6 Median price by MSOA.csv", "SC SF1 Air pollution.xlsx_SC SF1 Air Pollution.csv", "Report 1748 & Background DataV1.xlsx_Table 5.4.csv", "main-tables.xls_2.4.csv", "2csj3h29fr-1.zip_full_table_202004060334-TCNJ6C9A7M6N71CB_GIGMd_Trinity_Assembly.tsv.csv", "10s0007.xls_2000, April (Estimates Base).csv", "10s0007.xls_2005.csv", "10s0007.xls_2006.csv", "10s0007.xls_2007.csv", "10s0007.xls_2004.csv", "10s0070.xls_Data.csv", "C10093_C10093.csv", "C10159_C10159.csv", "C10020_C10020.csv", "C10087_C10087.csv", "C10044_C10044.csv", "C10096_C10096.csv", "C10142_C10142.csv", "C10062_C10062.csv", "C10013_C10013.csv", "Table_80_Full_time_Law_Enforcement_Employees_Louisiana_by_Metropolitan_and_Nonmetropolitan_Counties_2017.xls_17tbl80la.csv", "07tbl80fl.xls_Sheet1.csv", "david_delainey__8083__ENA Status of Completed Reviews.xlsx_Sheet1.csv", "Report 1652 & Background Data_Final.xls_Table 5.1.csv", "C10051_C10051.csv", "C10179_C10179.csv"], "subtable-type": ["IAAAA", "XPIAAA", "LAAAA", "XIAAAA", "XAA", "XIAAAA", "XPPAAA", "XIAAAA", "IAAAA", "XPIAAA", "XIAAAA", "LAAAA", "PXAAA", "XPIAAA", "XIAAAA", "NAAAA", "ASXAAA", "SAAXA", "DAAA", "DAAA", "DAAA", "XIIAA", "IAAA", "AXAAAA", "XAAAXA", "XXXAA", "CAAAA", "CAAAA", "CAAAA", "CAAAA", "CAAAA", "NXAAAA", "AAA", "XAAAAA", "PAAAA", "AIAAA", "IAAAA", "WAAAA", "BAAAA", "AIAAA", "AIAAA", "XPAAA", "XIAAA", "PSAAA", "XXAAA", "XAAAA", "XAAAA"], "table-type": "XSAAA"}